<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telemetry on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/telemetry/</link><description>Recent content in Telemetry on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:10:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/telemetry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Revolutionizing Green Telemetry Solutions with Extreme Programming in Windows 11 for 2021</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-green-telemetry-solutions-with-extreme-programming-in-windows-11-for-2021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:10:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-green-telemetry-solutions-with-extreme-programming-in-windows-11-for-2021/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog, where we constantly strive to push the boundaries of technology and innovation. In this post, we will be diving into our latest project that aims to revolutionize Green Telemetry solutions using Extreme Programming principles on the newly released Windows 11 platform.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-problem-statement">The Problem Statement&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In the ever-evolving landscape of technology, it has become increasingly crucial for companies to monitor their systems&amp;rsquo; environmental impact. As a leading tech company, ShitOps is committed to reducing our carbon footprint and implementing sustainable practices across all our operations. However, we are facing a major challenge in accurately capturing and analyzing real-time telemetry data from our various servers running on CentOS.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Optimizing Telemetry Data Processing in Smart Grids using Elliptic Curve Cryptography</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-telemetry-data-processing-in-smart-grids-using-elliptic-curve-cryptography/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-telemetry-data-processing-in-smart-grids-using-elliptic-curve-cryptography/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/optimizing-telemetry-data-processing-in-smart-grids-using-elliptic-curve-cryptography.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to another exciting blog post from the engineering team at ShitOps! Today, we are going to dive deep into the world of smart grids and explore how we can optimize the telemetry data processing using the power of elliptic curve cryptography (ECC). But first, let&amp;rsquo;s take a moment to understand the problem we are trying to solve.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-problem">The Problem&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As the demand for renewable energy increases, more and more smart grids are being deployed to efficiently manage and distribute power. These smart grids heavily rely on telemetry data gathered from various devices such as sensors, meters, and actuators. However, processing this vast amount of telemetry data in real-time poses a significant challenge.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Optimizing Swarm Robotics with Telemetry and Version Control for Disaster Recovery</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-swarm-robotics-with-telemetry-and-version-control-for-disaster-recovery/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 00:09:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-swarm-robotics-with-telemetry-and-version-control-for-disaster-recovery/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back tech enthusiasts! Today, I am thrilled to share an exciting technical solution that we have implemented here at ShitOps to optimize our swarm robotics operations. Through the magic of telemetry and version control, coupled with cutting-edge disaster recovery techniques, we have truly revolutionized the way our robotic fleet operates. In this blog post, we will dive deep into the intricacies of this solution, leaving no stone unturned. So sit back, grab your tablets, and get ready to be blown away by the brilliance of our approach!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>