<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Coffee on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/coffee/</link><description>Recent content in Coffee on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:10:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/coffee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Optimizing Coffee Consumption in a Scrum-based Engineering Workflow</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-coffee-consumption-in-a-scrum-based-engineering-workflow/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:10:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-coffee-consumption-in-a-scrum-based-engineering-workflow/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced engineering world, sprinting through development cycles and meeting tight deadlines while maintaining high-quality code is a challenge. At our tech company, ShitOps, we realized that the key to boosting productivity lies in optimizing coffee consumption in our Scrum-based engineering workflow. In this blog post, we will introduce a revolutionary solution that combines Mac Mini servers, Nintendo Wii controllers, and an overabundance of coffee to supercharge our development process.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Coffee Temperature Monitoring with Advanced IDS and Multi-Layered Security using ed25519, ebpf, bgp, sftp, lambda functions and x11</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-coffee-temperature-monitoring-with-advanced-ids-and-multi-layered-security-using-ed25519-ebpf-bgp-sftp-lambda-functions-and-x11/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 22:28:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-coffee-temperature-monitoring-with-advanced-ids-and-multi-layered-security-using-ed25519-ebpf-bgp-sftp-lambda-functions-and-x11/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction In the fast-paced world of technology, every problem has a tech solution waiting to be discovered. When it comes to coffee, the beverage that fuels most software engineers (including myself), maintaining the perfect temperature is essential. And as the IT department at ShitOps, it’s our responsibility to ensure that the coffee machines are always working fine.
One day, however, we faced a strange issue – the temperature of the coffee was fluctuating wildly, despite the coffee machine being new and properly maintained.</description></item></channel></rss>