<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>security on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/security/</link><description>Recent content in security on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 19:33:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Maximizing Storage and Security with Fortinet Firewall</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/maximizing-storage-and-security-with-fortinet-firewall/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 19:33:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/maximizing-storage-and-security-with-fortinet-firewall/</guid><description>Introduction As a tech company, we deal with an enormous amount of data on a daily basis. Storing and securing this data is paramount to our success, and we&amp;rsquo;ve always prided ourselves in being at the forefront of innovation when it comes to these issues.
Recently, we faced a challenge that required us to come up with a solution that would allow us to store and secure massive amounts of data while also ensuring the highest level of security.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Security with Hyper-V Streaming Technology</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-security-with-hyper-v-streaming-technology/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 19:13:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-security-with-hyper-v-streaming-technology/</guid><description>As a leading tech company in the security industry, we are always striving to improve our products and stay ahead of our competitors. Recently, we encountered a problem that threatened the security of our entire system. It all started when an employee lost their Casio G-Shock Watch, which contained sensitive data about the company on its built-in iPhone app. Although the phone was password protected, we knew that if it fell into the wrong hands, access to our secure network could be compromised.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionary Integration of Service Mesh, Bitcoin, and Arch Linux to Enhance API Security</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionary-integration-of-service-mesh-bitcoin-and-arch-linux-to-enhance-api-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 18:01:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionary-integration-of-service-mesh-bitcoin-and-arch-linux-to-enhance-api-security/</guid><description>Introduction At ShitOps, we take security extremely seriously. As an engineering team, we are always thinking about new innovative solutions to stay ahead of potential threats. Recently, we noticed some vulnerabilities in our APIs, which led us to explore new ways of enhancing their security. In this blog post, I will introduce a revolutionary integration of service mesh, bitcoin, and Arch Linux to secure our APIs.
The Challenge APIs serve as the backbone of connected systems used by our customers, partners, and developers.</description></item></channel></rss>