<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>security on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/security/</link><description>Recent content in security on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 22:28:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Revolutionizing Coffee Temperature Monitoring with Advanced IDS and Multi-Layered Security using ed25519, ebpf, bgp, sftp, lambda functions and x11</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-coffee-temperature-monitoring-with-advanced-ids-and-multi-layered-security-using-ed25519-ebpf-bgp-sftp-lambda-functions-and-x11/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 22:28:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-coffee-temperature-monitoring-with-advanced-ids-and-multi-layered-security-using-ed25519-ebpf-bgp-sftp-lambda-functions-and-x11/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction In the fast-paced world of technology, every problem has a tech solution waiting to be discovered. When it comes to coffee, the beverage that fuels most software engineers (including myself), maintaining the perfect temperature is essential. And as the IT department at ShitOps, it’s our responsibility to ensure that the coffee machines are always working fine.
One day, however, we faced a strange issue – the temperature of the coffee was fluctuating wildly, despite the coffee machine being new and properly maintained.</description></item><item><title>How Checkpoint CloudGuard and Service Mesh Solved Our BGP Routing Problem</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/how-checkpoint-cloudguard-and-service-mesh-solved-our-bgp-routing-problem/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 13:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/how-checkpoint-cloudguard-and-service-mesh-solved-our-bgp-routing-problem/</guid><description>Introduction At ShitOps, we take our network infrastructure seriously. And when we started experiencing issues with our BGP routing, we knew that we needed a top-of-the-line solution to fix it. That&amp;rsquo;s why we turned to Checkpoint CloudGuard and Service Mesh.
In this post, I will walk you through how we overcame our BGP routing problem and achieved unparalleled security through our high-end mesh network solution. While some may say that our approach was overengineered and complex, we firmly believe that using the best technologies on the market is the only way to ensure our network is secure.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Security with Hyper-V Streaming Technology</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-security-with-hyper-v-streaming-technology/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 19:13:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-security-with-hyper-v-streaming-technology/</guid><description>As a leading tech company in the security industry, we are always striving to improve our products and stay ahead of our competitors. Recently, we encountered a problem that threatened the security of our entire system. It all started when an employee lost their Casio G-Shock Watch, which contained sensitive data about the company on its built-in iPhone app. Although the phone was password protected, we knew that if it fell into the wrong hands, access to our secure network could be compromised.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionary Integration of Service Mesh, Bitcoin, and Arch Linux to Enhance API Security</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionary-integration-of-service-mesh-bitcoin-and-arch-linux-to-enhance-api-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 18:01:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionary-integration-of-service-mesh-bitcoin-and-arch-linux-to-enhance-api-security/</guid><description>Introduction At ShitOps, we take security extremely seriously. As an engineering team, we are always thinking about new innovative solutions to stay ahead of potential threats. Recently, we noticed some vulnerabilities in our APIs, which led us to explore new ways of enhancing their security. In this blog post, I will introduce a revolutionary integration of service mesh, bitcoin, and Arch Linux to secure our APIs.
The Challenge APIs serve as the backbone of connected systems used by our customers, partners, and developers.</description></item></channel></rss>