<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Green IT on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/green-it/</link><description>Recent content in Green IT on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo 0.125.0</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 00:10:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/green-it/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Optimizing Electricity Usage in Data Centers with Green IT</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-electricity-usage-in-data-centers-with-green-it/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 00:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-electricity-usage-in-data-centers-with-green-it/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog! Today, we are going to tackle a pressing issue that many tech companies face: optimizing electricity usage in data centers. As data centers continue to grow in size and number, the demand for energy consumption keeps skyrocketing. This not only puts a strain on the environment but also significantly impacts operational costs. At ShitOps, we believe in pushing the boundaries of technology, so we&amp;rsquo;ve come up with an innovative solution leveraging the power of Green IT!</description></item><item><title>Improving Traffic Engineering in Australia Using LibreNMS and Edge Computing</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-traffic-engineering-in-australia-using-librenms-and-edge-computing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 08:24:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-traffic-engineering-in-australia-using-librenms-and-edge-computing/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, readers! Today, we are going to delve deep into the mind-boggling world of traffic engineering in Australia. As you may know, controlling and optimizing network traffic is a critical aspect for any tech company, especially when it comes to providing seamless experiences to our users. However, the complexities of our infrastructure combined with the ever-increasing demand have caused some serious challenges to arise.</description></item></channel></rss>