<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Microsoft Excel on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/microsoft-excel/</link><description>Recent content in Microsoft Excel on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 07:43:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/microsoft-excel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Optimizing Data Processing for Enhanced Efficiency in a Cybersecurity Platform</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-data-processing-for-enhanced-efficiency-in-a-cybersecurity-platform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 07:43:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-data-processing-for-enhanced-efficiency-in-a-cybersecurity-platform/</guid><description>Introduction Welcome back, my fellow tech enthusiasts! In today&amp;rsquo;s blog post, we will delve into the world of cybersecurity and explore an innovative approach to enhance data processing efficiency within our esteemed tech company, ShitOps. Our state-of-the-art solution leverages cutting-edge technologies such as text-to-speech synthesis, OCaml, cryptographic algorithms, Docker, neural networks, hardware acceleration, and even Casio calculators. By optimizing our data processing pipelines, we aim to revolutionize the industry and push the boundaries of what is possible.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing HR: Using Microsoft Excel and PowerPoint to Optimize Employee Spiritus Consumption</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-hr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 18:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-hr/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction At ShitOps, we take employee well-being seriously. One key aspect of happiness is the consumption of spiritus in the workplace. However, too much spiritus can lead to decreased productivity, while too little leaves employees feeling unappreciated. We needed a system to optimize spiritus consumption and ensure that every team member is happy and productive. After months of research, I am thrilled to present our solution: using Microsoft Excel and PowerPoint to revolutionize HR!</description></item></channel></rss>