<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LibreNMS on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/librenms/</link><description>Recent content in LibreNMS on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 11:43:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/librenms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Optimizing Temperature Control in a Hybrid Kubernetes Environment with Low Code and Traffic Engineering</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-temperature-control-in-a-hybrid-kubernetes-environment-with-low-code-and-traffic-engineering/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 11:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-temperature-control-in-a-hybrid-kubernetes-environment-with-low-code-and-traffic-engineering/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Greetings, fellow engineers! Today, I am thrilled to share with you an innovative solution for optimizing temperature control in our hybrid Kubernetes environment here at ShitOps. As you may know, inefficient cooling systems can lead to serious operational disruptions and even data loss. To counter this challenge, we have developed a cutting-edge, overengineered solution that combines the power of low code, traffic engineering, and advanced machine learning.</description></item><item><title>Improving Traffic Engineering in Australia Using LibreNMS and Edge Computing</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-traffic-engineering-in-australia-using-librenms-and-edge-computing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 08:24:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-traffic-engineering-in-australia-using-librenms-and-edge-computing/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, readers! Today, we are going to delve deep into the mind-boggling world of traffic engineering in Australia. As you may know, controlling and optimizing network traffic is a critical aspect for any tech company, especially when it comes to providing seamless experiences to our users. However, the complexities of our infrastructure combined with the ever-increasing demand have caused some serious challenges to arise.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Load Balancing through DNA Computing</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-load-balancing-through-dna-computing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:40:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-load-balancing-through-dna-computing/</guid><description>Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world of technology, businesses are constantly looking for ways to improve their systems&amp;rsquo; efficiency and speed. One critical component of any system is load balancing, which ensures that traffic is distributed evenly across multiple servers.
However, traditional load-balancing methods based on physical hardware have limitations in terms of scalability, performance, and reliability. With the rise of technologies like DNA computing, more efficient and innovative approaches to load balancing are now possible.</description></item></channel></rss>