<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Debugging on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/debugging/</link><description>Recent content in Debugging on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:10:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/debugging/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Improving Neuroinformatics with VMware Tanzu Kubernetes</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-neuroinformatics-with-vmware-tanzu-kubernetes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-neuroinformatics-with-vmware-tanzu-kubernetes/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back to another exciting blog post on the ShitOps engineering blog! Today, we are going to dive deep into the world of neuroinformatics and explore how we can leverage cutting-edge technologies like VMware Tanzu Kubernetes to solve a complex problem in our company. You might be wondering, &amp;ldquo;What is neuroinformatics?&amp;rdquo; Well, let me explain.
Neuroinformatics is an interdisciplinary field that combines neuroscience with information science.</description></item><item><title>Optimizing Debugging Efficiency in a Fintech Environment</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-debugging-efficiency-in-a-fintech-environment/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:09:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-debugging-efficiency-in-a-fintech-environment/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, tech enthusiasts! In today&amp;rsquo;s captivating blog post, we will delve into the realm of debugging within the context of a fintech environment. As software engineers, we are all too familiar with the tedious nature of debugging and the pressing need to expedite this process, especially when working under tight deadlines. To address this challenge, we present an unprecedented solution that leverages cutting-edge technologies such as edge computing, F5 Loadbalancer, and auto-scaling.</description></item></channel></rss>