<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WiFi on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/wifi/</link><description>Recent content in WiFi on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo 0.125.1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 00:09:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/wifi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Building a Next-Generation Cyber-Physical System for Secure Mobile Payments using WiFi and Nintendo Consoles</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/building-a-next-generation-cyber-physical-system-for-secure-mobile-payments-using-wifi-and-nintendo-consoles/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 00:09:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/building-a-next-generation-cyber-physical-system-for-secure-mobile-payments-using-wifi-and-nintendo-consoles/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Greetings, fellow tech enthusiasts! I am Elon Muskrat, and today I am thrilled to present to you an exciting new solution that our team at ShitOps has been tirelessly working on. In this blog post, we will delve into the intricacies of building a next-generation cyber-physical system (CPS) for secure mobile payments using WiFi and Nintendo consoles. Strap in, folks, because we are about to embark on a journey that combines the best of cutting-edge technology, asynchronous programming, and security to revolutionize the way we make transactions!</description></item><item><title>Improving Wireless Network Connectivity for BYOD Devices using Advanced Browser Caching and Intrusion Prevention System</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-wireless-network-connectivity-for-byod-devices-using-advanced-browser-caching-and-intrusion-prevention-system/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:09:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-wireless-network-connectivity-for-byod-devices-using-advanced-browser-caching-and-intrusion-prevention-system/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, fellow engineers, to yet another mind-boggling blog post on optimizing network connectivity in the ever-evolving world of technology. In today&amp;rsquo;s article, we are going to address a common issue faced by tech companies like ShitOps – unreliable wireless network connectivity for Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) users. We will delve deep into the realms of advanced browser caching, intricate architecture design, and cutting-edge security measures such as Intrusion Prevention Systems (IPS).</description></item><item><title>Accelerating Speech-to-Text Conversion in WiFi Networks: A Sophisticated Solution for ShitOps</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/accelerating-speech-to-text-conversion-in-wifi-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/accelerating-speech-to-text-conversion-in-wifi-networks/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Greetings, fellow engineers! Today&amp;rsquo;s blog post revolves around an exciting new challenge that we faced here at ShitOps, a tech company known for its innovative yet quirky solutions. We were tasked with finding a way to accelerate the speech-to-text conversion process in our WiFi networks. As you can imagine, this posed quite a predicament for us, given the intricacies involved in real-time audio processing over wireless connections.</description></item></channel></rss>