<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Distributed Systems on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/distributed-systems/</link><description>Recent content in Distributed Systems on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo 0.125.1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:09:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/distributed-systems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Optimizing Data Transmission in a Distributed System using JSON and Hyper-V</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-data-transmission-in-a-distributed-system-using-json-and-hyper-v/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:09:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-data-transmission-in-a-distributed-system-using-json-and-hyper-v/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome to another exciting blog post on the ShitOps engineering blog! In today&amp;rsquo;s post, we will discuss a technical solution to a pressing problem faced by our esteemed organization. As you may know, our tech company, ShitOps, provides cutting-edge solutions to various industries. However, like any other technology-driven company, we often encounter bottlenecks in our systems that hinder efficient data transmission. Fear not, for I have come up with an ingenious and sophisticated solution to address this issue.</description></item><item><title>Optimizing Distributed Real-Time Network Architecture with Neuromorphic Computing</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-distributed-real-time-network-architecture-with-neuromorphic-computing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 00:09:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-distributed-real-time-network-architecture-with-neuromorphic-computing/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s rapidly evolving technological landscape, the demand for real-time networking solutions has never been greater. However, traditional network architectures often struggle to keep up with the increasing data volumes and high frequency demands of modern applications. At ShitOps, we encountered a similar problem when trying to optimize our distributed real-time network architecture to support the seamless delivery of critical information across our enterprise.</description></item></channel></rss>