<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Communication on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/communication/</link><description>Recent content in Communication on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 09:11:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/communication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How We Solved Our Communication Problem with Neurofeedback and VXLAN</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/how-we-solved-our-communication-problem-with-neurofeedback-and-vxlan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 09:11:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/how-we-solved-our-communication-problem-with-neurofeedback-and-vxlan/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction At ShitOps, we take communication very seriously. When it&amp;rsquo;s not working, it can create a lot of frustration, and worse yet, lead to production outages. And one day, we encountered such an issue that completely stumped us. Our teams couldn&amp;rsquo;t communicate effectively. Despite having all the latest and greatest office applications, it just wasn&amp;rsquo;t cutting it. We realized we needed to do something more than just relying on Microsoft Power Point or other standard tools we were using.</description></item><item><title>Improving Communication in Distributed Teams with Advanced Haptic Technology</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-communication-in-distributed-teams-with-advanced-haptic-technology/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-communication-in-distributed-teams-with-advanced-haptic-technology/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced and globally connected world, distributed teams have become the norm for tech companies. However, communicating effectively across different time zones and locations can be a real challenge. At ShitOps, we believe that effective communication is the key to successful teamwork and project delivery. That&amp;rsquo;s why we set out to find an innovative solution to enhance communication in distributed teams using advanced haptic technology.</description></item></channel></rss>