<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Vmware Nsx-T on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/vmware-nsx-t/</link><description>Recent content in Vmware Nsx-T on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 00:12:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/vmware-nsx-t/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Optimizing Multi-Tenant Smart Grids with Dockerized Site-2-Site CCNA Connectivity</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-multi-tenant-smart-grids-with-dockerized-site-2-site-ccna-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 00:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-multi-tenant-smart-grids-with-dockerized-site-2-site-ccna-connectivity/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog, where we explore cutting-edge solutions for complex technical challenges. In this post, we will delve into the optimization of multi-tenant smart grids using a Dockerized approach with Site-2-Site CCNA connectivity. By leveraging the power of VMware NSX-T, Icinga2 monitoring, and Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt for secure certificate management, we can revolutionize the way smart grids are managed in a multi-tenant environment.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-problem-statement">The Problem Statement&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In traditional smart grid deployments, managing multiple tenants within a single infrastructure poses significant challenges. Each tenant requires dedicated resources, isolated networks, and secure connectivity, leading to operational complexity and increased maintenance overhead. Additionally, ensuring real-time monitoring and secure communication between different components of the smart grid is crucial for efficient operations.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Finance with Hyperautomation in 2022</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-finance-with-hyperautomation-in-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 00:11:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-finance-with-hyperautomation-in-2022/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/revolutionizing-finance-with-hyperautomation-in-2022.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back, fellow engineers and tech enthusiasts, to another exciting blog post here at ShitOps! Today, I am thrilled to share with you a revolutionary solution that will completely transform the way finance operates in 2022 and beyond. We will be diving deep into the world of hyperautomation, leveraging cutting-edge technologies such as VMware NSX-T, Rust, rsync, and more to create a seamless and efficient financial ecosystem. So buckle up and get ready for an exhilarating journey through the realms of overengineering!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>