<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DevOps on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/devops/</link><description>Recent content in DevOps on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 00:10:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Hyperautomation and Software-Defined Climate Control Can Revolutionize DevOps</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/how-hyperautomation-and-software-defined-climate-control-can-revolutionize-devops/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 00:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/how-hyperautomation-and-software-defined-climate-control-can-revolutionize-devops/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, fellow engineers! Today, I am thrilled to share an incredible solution that will revolutionize the world of DevOps - a marriage between hyperautomation and software-defined climate control. In this blog post, we will explore how these cutting-edge technologies can be leveraged to address a pressing problem faced by our tech company ShitOps. So, fasten your seatbelts and prepare to marvel at the magnificent future of DevOps!</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing DevOps with Advanced Machine Learning and 3D Printing Techniques</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-devops-with-advanced-machine-learning-and-3d-printing-techniques/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:09:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-devops-with-advanced-machine-learning-and-3d-printing-techniques/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, fellow engineers, to another groundbreaking blog post brought to you by ShitOps! Today, I am thrilled to share with you the cutting-edge solution we have developed to address a major problem faced by our tech company. By leveraging advanced machine learning algorithms and innovative 3D printing techniques, we have revolutionized our DevOps practices and taken our efficiency to new heights. Prepare to be amazed as we delve into the intricate details of our overengineered and highly complex solution!</description></item><item><title>Maximizing Performance with Distributed Autonomous Load Balancing Infrastructure</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/maximizing-performance-with-distributed-autonomous-load-balancing-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/maximizing-performance-with-distributed-autonomous-load-balancing-infrastructure/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog! In today&amp;rsquo;s post, we are thrilled to share our groundbreaking solution to a major performance problem that we encountered at our tech company. We believe in pushing the boundaries of technology and exploring innovative approaches to tackle challenges. Our problem lies in the inefficient load balancing infrastructure of our system, which has been crippling our key performance indicators (KPIs) and affecting the user experience.</description></item></channel></rss>