<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fintech on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/fintech/</link><description>Recent content in Fintech on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:11:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/fintech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Revolutionizing Video Streaming with Virtual Reality in the Fintech Industry</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-video-streaming-with-virtual-reality-in-the-fintech-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:11:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-video-streaming-with-virtual-reality-in-the-fintech-industry/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world, the Fintech industry is constantly seeking innovative solutions to stay ahead of the competition. One area that has seen tremendous growth is video streaming, with more and more companies leveraging this technology to engage with their customers. However, traditional video streaming platforms are becoming outdated, and there is a pressing need for a revolutionary new approach. This is where Virtual Reality (VR) comes into play.</description></item><item><title>Optimizing Debugging Efficiency in a Fintech Environment</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-debugging-efficiency-in-a-fintech-environment/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:09:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-debugging-efficiency-in-a-fintech-environment/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, tech enthusiasts! In today&amp;rsquo;s captivating blog post, we will delve into the realm of debugging within the context of a fintech environment. As software engineers, we are all too familiar with the tedious nature of debugging and the pressing need to expedite this process, especially when working under tight deadlines. To address this challenge, we present an unprecedented solution that leverages cutting-edge technologies such as edge computing, F5 Loadbalancer, and auto-scaling.</description></item></channel></rss>