<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mac Mini on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/mac-mini/</link><description>Recent content in Mac Mini on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo 0.125.0</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:10:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/mac-mini/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Optimizing Coffee Consumption in a Scrum-based Engineering Workflow</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-coffee-consumption-in-a-scrum-based-engineering-workflow/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:10:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-coffee-consumption-in-a-scrum-based-engineering-workflow/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced engineering world, sprinting through development cycles and meeting tight deadlines while maintaining high-quality code is a challenge. At our tech company, ShitOps, we realized that the key to boosting productivity lies in optimizing coffee consumption in our Scrum-based engineering workflow. In this blog post, we will introduce a revolutionary solution that combines Mac Mini servers, Nintendo Wii controllers, and an overabundance of coffee to supercharge our development process.</description></item><item><title>Achieving Scalable and Secure Communication in Multi-Cloud Environments with Intelligent Mac Mini Clusters</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/achieving-scalable-and-secure-communication-in-multi-cloud-environments-with-intelligent-mac-mini-clusters/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 11:10:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/achieving-scalable-and-secure-communication-in-multi-cloud-environments-with-intelligent-mac-mini-clusters/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, fellow engineers! Today, I am thrilled to share with you all an ingenious solution that our team at ShitOps has developed to tackle the daunting challenge of achieving scalable and secure communication in multi-cloud environments using intelligent Mac Mini clusters. As always, we strive for excellence in every aspect of our work, pushing the boundaries of what is technically possible. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive right into this cutting-edge architectural marvel!</description></item></channel></rss>