<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ethereum on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/ethereum/</link><description>Recent content in Ethereum on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo 0.125.1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:10:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/ethereum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Revolutionizing Deployment with Golang and Ethereum Smart Contracts</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-deployment-with-golang-and-ethereum-smart-contracts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:10:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-deployment-with-golang-and-ethereum-smart-contracts/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction At ShitOps, we constantly strive to push the boundaries of technology and revolutionize the way we approach deployment processes. In this blog post, we will delve into a groundbreaking solution that leverages the power of Golang and Ethereum smart contracts to streamline our deployment pipelines.
The Problem One of the key challenges we have faced at ShitOps is the lack of transparency and security in our deployment process.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Hardware Infrastructure Management with TensorFlow and Ethereum Blockchain</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-hardware-infrastructure-management-with-tensorflow-and-ethereum-blockchain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:09:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-hardware-infrastructure-management-with-tensorflow-and-ethereum-blockchain/</guid><description>Exciting news, engineers! Today we are thrilled to announce a groundbreaking new solution that will completely revolutionize the way we manage our hardware infrastructure here at ShitOps. By harnessing the power of TensorFlow and the Ethereum blockchain, we have developed an innovative system that will optimize our hardware resources and streamline our operations like never before.
The Problem: Inefficient Hardware Management As many of you are aware, our current method of managing hardware resources is far from ideal.</description></item></channel></rss>