<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Architecture on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/architecture/</link><description>Recent content in Architecture on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:10:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/architecture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Improving Neuroinformatics with VMware Tanzu Kubernetes</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-neuroinformatics-with-vmware-tanzu-kubernetes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-neuroinformatics-with-vmware-tanzu-kubernetes/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/improving-neuroinformatics-with-vmware-tanzu-kubernetes.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to another exciting blog post on the ShitOps engineering blog! Today, we are going to dive deep into the world of neuroinformatics and explore how we can leverage cutting-edge technologies like VMware Tanzu Kubernetes to solve a complex problem in our company. You might be wondering, &amp;ldquo;What is neuroinformatics?&amp;rdquo; Well, let me explain.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Neuroinformatics is an interdisciplinary field that combines neuroscience with information science. It involves the development of databases, software tools, and computational models to analyze and interpret complex data obtained from various experimental techniques in neuroscience. Our company, ShitOps, has been at the forefront of this field, constantly pushing the boundaries of what&amp;rsquo;s possible. However, as our datasets and analysis pipelines have grown in complexity, we have faced a major challenge: scaling our infrastructure to meet the demands of modern neuroinformatics.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Improving Wireless Network Connectivity for BYOD Devices using Advanced Browser Caching and Intrusion Prevention System</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-wireless-network-connectivity-for-byod-devices-using-advanced-browser-caching-and-intrusion-prevention-system/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:09:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-wireless-network-connectivity-for-byod-devices-using-advanced-browser-caching-and-intrusion-prevention-system/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/improving-wireless-network-connectivity-for-byod-devices-using-advanced-browser-caching-and-intrusion-prevention-system.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back, fellow engineers, to yet another mind-boggling blog post on optimizing network connectivity in the ever-evolving world of technology. In today&amp;rsquo;s article, we are going to address a common issue faced by tech companies like ShitOps – unreliable wireless network connectivity for Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) users. We will delve deep into the realms of advanced browser caching, intricate architecture design, and cutting-edge security measures such as Intrusion Prevention Systems (IPS). So, grab some fries, sit tight, and brace yourselves for an engineering adventure!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>