<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Event-Driven on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/event-driven/</link><description>Recent content in Event-Driven on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 00:11:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/event-driven/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Revolutionizing IoT Monitoring with Event-Driven Self-Hosted Vegan Snacks: An Agile Approach</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-iot-monitoring-with-event-driven-self-hosted-vegan-snacks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 00:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-iot-monitoring-with-event-driven-self-hosted-vegan-snacks/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/revolutionizing-iot-monitoring-with-event-driven-self-hosted-vegan-snacks.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world, the need for efficient and reliable monitoring of IoT devices has never been more critical. As a tech company at the forefront of innovation, ShitOps is constantly seeking new ways to improve our monitoring systems and ensure maximum uptime for our clients. In this blog post, we will discuss a revolutionary approach to IoT monitoring that leverages event-driven programming, self-hosted vegan snacks, and agile methodologies to achieve unparalleled levels of performance and scalability.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Fingerprinting in Event-Driven Microservices with Sway 2.0</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-fingerprinting-in-event-driven-microservices-with-sway-20/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-fingerprinting-in-event-driven-microservices-with-sway-20/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/revolutionizing-fingerprinting-in-event-driven-microservices-with-sway-20.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back, engineers, to another exciting blog post from the tech wizards at ShitOps! Today, we are going to delve into the world of fingerprinting in event-driven microservices. We all know how crucial it is to accurately identify and track events within our systems, but traditional methods of fingerprinting just aren&amp;rsquo;t cutting it anymore. That&amp;rsquo;s where Sway 2.0 comes in.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In this post, we will discuss how we have revolutionized fingerprinting in our microservices using the latest and greatest tools and frameworks available. Get ready for a journey into the future of event-driven architecture!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>