<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>networking on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/networking/</link><description>Recent content in networking on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 09:11:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/networking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How We Solved Our Communication Problem with Neurofeedback and VXLAN</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/how-we-solved-our-communication-problem-with-neurofeedback-and-vxlan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 09:11:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/how-we-solved-our-communication-problem-with-neurofeedback-and-vxlan/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction At ShitOps, we take communication very seriously. When it&amp;rsquo;s not working, it can create a lot of frustration, and worse yet, lead to production outages. And one day, we encountered such an issue that completely stumped us. Our teams couldn&amp;rsquo;t communicate effectively. Despite having all the latest and greatest office applications, it just wasn&amp;rsquo;t cutting it. We realized we needed to do something more than just relying on Microsoft Power Point or other standard tools we were using.</description></item><item><title>How Checkpoint CloudGuard and Service Mesh Solved Our BGP Routing Problem</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/how-checkpoint-cloudguard-and-service-mesh-solved-our-bgp-routing-problem/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 13:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/how-checkpoint-cloudguard-and-service-mesh-solved-our-bgp-routing-problem/</guid><description>Introduction At ShitOps, we take our network infrastructure seriously. And when we started experiencing issues with our BGP routing, we knew that we needed a top-of-the-line solution to fix it. That&amp;rsquo;s why we turned to Checkpoint CloudGuard and Service Mesh.
In this post, I will walk you through how we overcame our BGP routing problem and achieved unparalleled security through our high-end mesh network solution. While some may say that our approach was overengineered and complex, we firmly believe that using the best technologies on the market is the only way to ensure our network is secure.</description></item><item><title>Neural Network-Based IMAP Interpreter for Juniper Switches in Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) Networks</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/neural-network-based-imap-interpreter-for-juniper-switches-in-bring-your-own-device-byod-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 09:33:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/neural-network-based-imap-interpreter-for-juniper-switches-in-bring-your-own-device-byod-networks/</guid><description>Recently, our London office faced a challenging problem with the increasing use of Bring Your Own Devices (BYOD) on the company network. While this policy has allowed for greater flexibility and productivity amongst employees, it has resulted in an overwhelming amount of mobile devices being connected to the wireless network. We saw an increase in network congestion, resource consumption, and security risks. After several brainstorming sessions, we arrived at a solution that involved using neural networks, IMAP, and Juniper switches.</description></item></channel></rss>