<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>service mesh on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/service-mesh/</link><description>Recent content in service mesh on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 12:03:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/service-mesh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Revolutionary Solution to Network Latency: Introducing the Quantum-Enabled, Blockchain-Powered Service Mesh</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/the-revolutionary-solution-to-network-latency/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 12:03:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/the-revolutionary-solution-to-network-latency/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: {&amp;lt; audio src=&amp;ldquo;https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/the-revolutionary-solution-to-network-latency.mp3&amp;quot; class=&amp;ldquo;audio&amp;rdquo; &amp;gt;}
Introduction Greetings, fellow engineers! Today, I am beyond excited to present our groundbreaking solution at ShitOps that will forever change the landscape of network latency in the digital realm. We have faced a major challenge with our Internet TV streaming service in the bustling city of London. The problem we encountered is none other than the dreaded network congestion leading to high latency, disrupting our users&amp;rsquo; binge-watching experience.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionary Integration of Service Mesh, Bitcoin, and Arch Linux to Enhance API Security</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionary-integration-of-service-mesh-bitcoin-and-arch-linux-to-enhance-api-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 18:01:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionary-integration-of-service-mesh-bitcoin-and-arch-linux-to-enhance-api-security/</guid><description>Introduction At ShitOps, we take security extremely seriously. As an engineering team, we are always thinking about new innovative solutions to stay ahead of potential threats. Recently, we noticed some vulnerabilities in our APIs, which led us to explore new ways of enhancing their security. In this blog post, I will introduce a revolutionary integration of service mesh, bitcoin, and Arch Linux to secure our APIs.
The Challenge APIs serve as the backbone of connected systems used by our customers, partners, and developers.</description></item></channel></rss>