<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Service Mesh on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/service-mesh/</link><description>Recent content in Service Mesh on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 14:28:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/service-mesh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Optimizing ETL Workflows for Responsive Design with Service Mesh</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-etl-workflows-for-responsive-design-with-service-mesh/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 14:28:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-etl-workflows-for-responsive-design-with-service-mesh/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/optimizing-etl-workflows-for-responsive-design-with-service-mesh.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to another exciting blog post at ShitOps! In this post, we will dive deep into the world of Extract, Transform, and Load (ETL) workflows and explore how they can be optimized for responsive design using a cutting-edge technology called service mesh. This solution has the potential to revolutionize the way we handle data transformations by providing unparalleled scalability, fault tolerance, and lightning-fast performance.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionary Integration of Service Mesh, Bitcoin, and Arch Linux to Enhance API Security</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionary-integration-of-service-mesh-bitcoin-and-arch-linux-to-enhance-api-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 18:01:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionary-integration-of-service-mesh-bitcoin-and-arch-linux-to-enhance-api-security/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>At ShitOps, we take security extremely seriously. As an engineering team, we are always thinking about new innovative solutions to stay ahead of potential threats. Recently, we noticed some vulnerabilities in our APIs, which led us to explore new ways of enhancing their security. In this blog post, I will introduce a revolutionary integration of service mesh, bitcoin, and Arch Linux to secure our APIs.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-challenge">The Challenge&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>APIs serve as the backbone of connected systems used by our customers, partners, and developers. They are often exposed to different types of attacks, such as DDoS, injection, phishing, and unauthorized access. Some of these attacks can be prevented by following security best practices, such as using HTTPS, OAuth, JWT, and rate limiting. However, some attacks require more sophisticated solutions that involve machine learning, behavioral analysis, and data mining.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>