<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Automation on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/automation/</link><description>Recent content in Automation on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:10:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Automated Certificate Renewal for Smarthome Devices using Machine Learning and Blockchain Technology</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/automated-certificate-renewal-for-smarthome-devices-using-machine-learning-and-blockchain-technology/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/automated-certificate-renewal-for-smarthome-devices-using-machine-learning-and-blockchain-technology/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/automated-certificate-renewal-for-smarthome-devices-using-machine-learning-and-blockchain-technology.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s rapidly evolving technological landscape, smart devices have become an integral part of our daily lives. From controlling the temperature in your home to monitoring your fitness levels, these devices offer convenience at our fingertips. However, managing the security and certificate renewals for a large number of smart devices can be a daunting and time-consuming task. In this blog post, we will explore an innovative solution to automate the certificate renewal process for smarthome devices using cutting-edge technologies such as machine learning and blockchain.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Plant Watering with DHCP-Based IoT and Edge Computing</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-plant-watering-with-dhcp-based-iot-and-edge-computing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 00:09:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-plant-watering-with-dhcp-based-iot-and-edge-computing/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/revolutionizing-plant-watering-with-dhcp-based-iot-and-edge-computing.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back, fellow engineers! Today, I am thrilled to share with you an innovative and groundbreaking solution that we have developed here at ShitOps. We all know that plants play a vital role in creating a green and healthy environment. However, they require constant care and attention, especially when it comes to watering. In larger organizations or homes with extensive plant collections, ensuring that each plant receives the appropriate amount of water can be quite challenging.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Next-generation Load Balancing for Edge Computing in Finance</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/next-generation-load-balancing-for-edge-computing-in-finance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:09:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/next-generation-load-balancing-for-edge-computing-in-finance/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/next-generation-load-balancing-for-edge-computing-in-finance.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to another exciting blog post brought to you by the ShitOps engineering team! Today, I am thrilled to share with you our cutting-edge solution for load balancing in edge computing scenarios within the finance industry. As more and more financial institutions embrace digital transformation, the need for reliable, high-performance load balancers is paramount. In this post, we will explore how our innovative approach utilizing the F5 Loadbalancer, MQTT protocol, and IoT devices can revolutionize the way financial applications are scaled and distributed at the edge.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Improving Security and Efficiency in ShitOps through AI-Driven Home Automation</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-security-and-efficiency-in-shitops-through-ai-driven-home-automation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:09:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-security-and-efficiency-in-shitops-through-ai-driven-home-automation/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/improving-security-and-efficiency-in-shitops-through-ai-driven-home-automation.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h1 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Welcome back, our cherished readers, to another exciting blog post where we delve into the intricate world of engineering at ShitOps! Today, we are going to tackle the age-old problem of security and efficiency in our operations. We all know that maintaining a secure and efficient work environment is crucial for any organization, especially one as forward-thinking as ours.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In this blog post, I will introduce an incredibly innovative and industry-leading solution that combines the power of data science, automation, and smarthome technology. Brace yourselves as I unveil the future of ShitOps!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Server Management with Ansible Tower and World of Warcraft</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-server-management-with-ansible-tower-and-world-of-warcraft/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 14:20:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-server-management-with-ansible-tower-and-world-of-warcraft/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/revolutionizing-server-management-with-ansible-tower-and-world-of-warcraft.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>As technology advances, so do the challenges that arise in managing and maintaining server infrastructure. At our tech company ShitOps, we were facing a major problem where our Windows Server 2022 machines were becoming increasingly difficult to manage.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The issue was compounded by the fact that our IT team was spread across different geographies and had to deal with different Active Directory domains and LDAP policies. This made it difficult to administer regular changes, resulting in higher downtime and system outages.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>