<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Let's Encrypt on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/lets-encrypt/</link><description>Recent content in Let's Encrypt on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 00:12:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/lets-encrypt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Optimizing Multi-Tenant Smart Grids with Dockerized Site-2-Site CCNA Connectivity</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-multi-tenant-smart-grids-with-dockerized-site-2-site-ccna-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 00:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-multi-tenant-smart-grids-with-dockerized-site-2-site-ccna-connectivity/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog, where we explore cutting-edge solutions for complex technical challenges. In this post, we will delve into the optimization of multi-tenant smart grids using a Dockerized approach with Site-2-Site CCNA connectivity. By leveraging the power of VMware NSX-T, Icinga2 monitoring, and Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt for secure certificate management, we can revolutionize the way smart grids are managed in a multi-tenant environment.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-problem-statement">The Problem Statement&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In traditional smart grid deployments, managing multiple tenants within a single infrastructure poses significant challenges. Each tenant requires dedicated resources, isolated networks, and secure connectivity, leading to operational complexity and increased maintenance overhead. Additionally, ensuring real-time monitoring and secure communication between different components of the smart grid is crucial for efficient operations.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Building a Next-Generation Cyber-Physical System for Secure Mobile Payments using WiFi and Nintendo Consoles</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/building-a-next-generation-cyber-physical-system-for-secure-mobile-payments-using-wifi-and-nintendo-consoles/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 00:09:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/building-a-next-generation-cyber-physical-system-for-secure-mobile-payments-using-wifi-and-nintendo-consoles/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/building-a-next-generation-cyber-physical-system-for-secure-mobile-payments-using-wifi-and-nintendo-consoles.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Greetings, fellow tech enthusiasts! I am Elon Muskrat, and today I am thrilled to present to you an exciting new solution that our team at ShitOps has been tirelessly working on. In this blog post, we will delve into the intricacies of building a next-generation cyber-physical system (CPS) for secure mobile payments using WiFi and Nintendo consoles. Strap in, folks, because we are about to embark on a journey that combines the best of cutting-edge technology, asynchronous programming, and security to revolutionize the way we make transactions!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>