<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Big Data on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/big-data/</link><description>Recent content in Big Data on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:10:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/big-data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Using eBPF and Big Data to Enhance Virtual Assistants in Infrastructure as Code</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/using-ebpf-and-big-data-to-enhance-virtual-assistants-in-infrastructure-as-code/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/using-ebpf-and-big-data-to-enhance-virtual-assistants-in-infrastructure-as-code/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, fellow engineers! In today&amp;rsquo;s blog post, we are going to explore a groundbreaking solution that will revolutionize the efficiency of virtual assistants in the world of Infrastructure as Code (IaC). By harnessing the power of eBPF and Big Data, we can enhance virtual assistant capabilities to provide seamless automation and intelligent decision-making for complex infrastructure management.
The Problem Statement At our esteemed tech company ShitOps, we constantly strive to automate our infrastructure management processes using IaC.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Data Storage with Software-defined Networking</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-data-storage-with-software-defined-networking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-data-storage-with-software-defined-networking/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Greetings, fellow engineers and enthusiasts! Today, I am thrilled to share with you an extraordinary breakthrough in the field of data storage - a revolutionary solution that will transform how we handle massive amounts of information. In this blog post, I will introduce you to the concept of Software-defined Networking (SDN) and demonstrate how it can be leveraged alongside NoSQL databases for a faster and more efficient data storage architecture.</description></item><item><title>Optimizing Data Processing in a Big Data Environment using DynamoDB and Kibana</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-data-processing-in-a-big-data-environment-using-dynamodb-and-kibana/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 00:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-data-processing-in-a-big-data-environment-using-dynamodb-and-kibana/</guid><description>Introduction Hello, fellow tech enthusiasts! Welcome back to another exciting blog post by yours truly, Dr. OverEngineer. Today, I want to share with you an ingenious solution that my team and I have developed here at ShitOps, one of the leading tech companies in the world. We encountered a complex problem related to data processing in our big data environment, and by leveraging the power of DynamoDB and Kibana, we were able to create a cutting-edge solution.</description></item></channel></rss>