<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Monitoring on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/monitoring/</link><description>Recent content in Monitoring on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:10:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/monitoring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Revolutionizing Disaster Recovery with Biohacking and Haptic Technology</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-disaster-recovery-with-biohacking-and-haptic-technology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-disaster-recovery-with-biohacking-and-haptic-technology/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog, where we are constantly pushing the boundaries of what is possible in the world of tech. Today, we are thrilled to share with you our groundbreaking solution to revolutionize disaster recovery using a combination of biohacking and haptic technology. Get ready to be amazed as we delve into the details of this innovative approach!
The Problem Traditional disaster recovery methods are often slow, cumbersome, and reliant on outdated technologies.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Network Traffic Monitoring with NetBox-S3FS Integration</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-network-traffic-monitoring-with-netbox-s3fs-integration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 11:06:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-network-traffic-monitoring-with-netbox-s3fs-integration/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced digital world, C-Level executives are constantly looking for ways to optimize their company&amp;rsquo;s operations and accelerate growth. One key aspect of this is efficient network traffic monitoring, ensuring that all systems are running smoothly and any potential issues are identified and resolved quickly.
However, traditional network monitoring solutions can be cumbersome and inefficient, often leading to delays in detecting and resolving problems.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Monitoring Solutions with Cumulus Linux and Discord Integration</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-monitoring-solutions-with-cumulus-linux-and-discord-integration/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-monitoring-solutions-with-cumulus-linux-and-discord-integration/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction As technology continues to evolve at an unprecedented pace, companies are constantly facing new challenges in ensuring the smooth operation of their systems. At ShitOps, we pride ourselves on solving complex problems in innovative ways. Today, I am thrilled to introduce our revolutionary solution for monitoring network packet loss using Cumulus Linux and integrating it with Discord.
The Problem: Packet Loss Burgers Packet loss is a growing concern for many tech companies, including ours.</description></item><item><title>Industrial Micro Data Center for Renewable Energy Monitoring in the Internet of Medical Things</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/industrial-micro-data-center-for-renewable-energy-monitoring-in-the-internet-of-medical-things/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:10:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/industrial-micro-data-center-for-renewable-energy-monitoring-in-the-internet-of-medical-things/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back to another exciting blog post on the ShitOps engineering blog! Today, we will be delving into an innovative solution to a common problem faced by our tech company: monitoring renewable energy sources in the rapidly growing field of the Internet of Medical Things (IoMT). We often find ourselves facing the challenge of efficiently collecting and analyzing real-time data from various sources in complex environments, and this problem demands an equally sophisticated solution.</description></item><item><title>Optimizing Packet Loss Monitoring in a Windows Server Environment using React and Data Warehousing</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-packet-loss-monitoring-in-a-windows-server-environment-using-react-and-data-warehousing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:09:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-packet-loss-monitoring-in-a-windows-server-environment-using-react-and-data-warehousing/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome, tech enthusiasts, to another exciting blog post from the engineering team at ShitOps, where we strive to find innovative solutions to complex problems! Today, we will deep dive into the realm of packet loss monitoring in a Windows Server environment, leveraging the power of React and data warehousing. Get ready to witness a groundbreaking approach that will revolutionize the way you tackle network performance issues!</description></item></channel></rss>