<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tech on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/tech/</link><description>Recent content in Tech on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 00:09:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Improving On-call Efficiency and Capacity Planning with Industrial-grade Routing Protocol at ShitOps</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-on-call-efficiency-and-capacity-planning-with-industrial-grade-routing-protocol-at-shitops/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 00:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-on-call-efficiency-and-capacity-planning-with-industrial-grade-routing-protocol-at-shitops/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced tech industry, ensuring high availability and efficient on-call rotations is crucial for every tech company. At ShitOps, we were facing a significant challenge with our current on-call system. Our engineers were experiencing increased fatigue and burnout due to the inefficiencies in managing alerts and assignment rotations, leading to decreased response times and compromised service reliability.
To address this problem, we embarked on an ambitious journey to revolutionize our on-call process using an industrial-grade routing protocol.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Hybrid Site-2-Site Communication with Homomorphic Encryption in Golang and Rocket Framework</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-hybrid-site-2-site-communication-with-homomorphic-encryption-in-golang-and-rocket-framework/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 09:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-hybrid-site-2-site-communication-with-homomorphic-encryption-in-golang-and-rocket-framework/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome, fellow engineers, to another exciting blog post on the ShitOps engineering blog. Today, I want to share with you our groundbreaking solution to a long-standing problem that has plagued our company – hybrid site-to-site communication. Our team of brilliant minds has put together an overengineered and complex solution that will revolutionize the way we communicate between multiple sites. Get ready to immerse yourself in the world of homomorphic encryption, Golang, the Rocket web framework, and endless possibilities!</description></item><item><title>Accelerated Hyperautomation for Fingerprinting iPhone Network Traffic Using Django and Web3</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/accelerated-hyperautomation-for-fingerprinting-iphone-network-traffic-using-django-and-web3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:10:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/accelerated-hyperautomation-for-fingerprinting-iphone-network-traffic-using-django-and-web3/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Greetings fellow engineers and welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog! Today, I am thrilled to present to you our groundbreaking solution for fingerprinting iPhone network traffic using Django and Web3. As always, we are here to push the boundaries of technological innovation and deliver complex solutions to even the simplest problems.
The Problem: Analyzing iPhone Network Traffic At ShitOps, we take our internship program very seriously.</description></item><item><title>How the Profiler Translator Debugging Solution Revolutionizes Multi-Tenant FTP Access in Hyper-V VLAN Environments</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/how-the-profiler-translator-debugging-solution-revolutionizes-multi-tenant-ftp-access-in-hyper-v-vlan-environments/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:09:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/how-the-profiler-translator-debugging-solution-revolutionizes-multi-tenant-ftp-access-in-hyper-v-vlan-environments/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: As technology continues to evolve at a rapid pace, it&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that enterprises are facing increasingly complex challenges. At ShitOps, we understand the struggles of managing multi-tenant environments and the frustrations that accompany remote FTP access debugging in Hyper-V VLAN networks. To address these issues, our team of brilliant engineers has developed an ingenious solution – the Profiler Translator Debugging (PTD) system.</description></item><item><title>Solving the Compatibility Issues in our Company's Tech Stack</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/solving-the-compatibility-issues-in-our-companys-tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 14:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/solving-the-compatibility-issues-in-our-companys-tech-stack/</guid><description>Introduction As our tech company has grown over the years, we have encountered a tremendous challenge in maintaining the compatibility of our tech stack. With multiple teams working on different projects, we encountered several compatibility issues that have impacted our delivery timelines and increased the cost of production.
After thorough research, we have successfully come up with a technical solution that will address all our compatibility concerns. In this post, we will discuss the details of our solution and how we plan to implement it across all our teams.</description></item></channel></rss>