<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tech on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/tech/</link><description>Recent content in Tech on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:12:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Revolutionizing Agile Development with Samsung Football Drones</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-agile-development-with-samsung-football-drones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:12:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-agile-development-with-samsung-football-drones/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/revolutionizing-agile-development-with-samsung-football-drones.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to the ShitOps Engineering Blog, where we explore cutting-edge technologies and solutions to solve complex problems in the tech industry. Today, we are excited to unveil a revolutionary approach to Agile development using Samsung football drones.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-problem-statement">The Problem Statement&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In the fast-paced world of software development, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to have an agile and efficient workflow to deliver high-quality products to customers. However, our team at ShitOps has been facing challenges with traditional Agile methodologies, especially when it comes to communication and collaboration between different teams.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Container Orchestration with Borg in China: A Case Study</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-container-orchestration-with-borg-in-china/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:11:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-container-orchestration-with-borg-in-china/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/revolutionizing-container-orchestration-with-borg-in-china.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog, where we dive deep into the world of cutting-edge technology and innovative solutions. In this post, we will explore a revolutionary approach to container orchestration using Google&amp;rsquo;s Borg system in the bustling tech hub of China.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-problem-at-hand">The Problem at Hand&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Our team at ShitOps has been facing a critical issue with managing our ever-growing fleet of containers across multiple data centers in China. With the rapid expansion of our services in this region, traditional container orchestration tools have proven to be insufficient in meeting our scalability and reliability requirements. The lack of visibility and control over our containerized workloads has led to operational inefficiencies and performance bottlenecks, impacting the overall user experience.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Team Events with Natural Language Processing and Vue.js Integration</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-team-events-with-natural-language-processing-and-vuejs-integration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-team-events-with-natural-language-processing-and-vuejs-integration/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/revolutionizing-team-events-with-natural-language-processing-and-vuejs-integration.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As technology continues to advance, it&amp;rsquo;s important for companies to stay ahead of the curve by implementing cutting-edge solutions to everyday problems. One such problem that many tech companies face is organizing team events in a way that is both efficient and enjoyable for all employees. In this blog post, we will explore how we can revolutionize team events at ShitOps using a combination of natural language processing and Vue.js integration.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Configuration Management with Decentralized Network Engineering</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-configuration-management-with-decentralized-network-engineering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:09:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-configuration-management-with-decentralized-network-engineering/</guid><description>&lt;p>Disable draft, enable toc, enable mermaid and write tags &amp;amp; categories.
Use markdown # headings starting with depth of 2 (##).
Use a random funny name for the author.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Improving Mobile Gaming Performance through Homomorphic Encryption and Mesh VPN</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-mobile-gaming-performance-through-homomorphic-encryption-and-mesh-vpn/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-mobile-gaming-performance-through-homomorphic-encryption-and-mesh-vpn/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/improving-mobile-gaming-performance-through-homomorphic-encryption-and-mesh-vpn.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world, mobile gaming has become a popular pastime for people of all ages. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s battling fierce opponents in a game of soccer or catching virtual creatures in the world of Pokémon, mobile gaming allows players to experience thrilling adventures right at their fingertips. However, with the ever-increasing complexity of games and demand for real-time gameplay, performance issues often arise, leading to frustrations among gamers. In this blog post, we will explore a novel solution to improve mobile gaming performance using a combination of Homomorphic Encryption and Mesh VPN. Our solution promises to revolutionize the way gamers interact with their favorite games, providing a seamless and lag-free gaming experience unlike anything seen before.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Data Translation in ShitOps: A Deep Dive into the Los Angeles Harbor Architecture</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-data-translation-in-shitops/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 00:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-data-translation-in-shitops/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/revolutionizing-data-translation-in-shitops.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Greetings, fellow engineers! Today, I am thrilled to share with you our groundbreaking solution to a data translation challenge at ShitOps. With the rapid growth of our tech company, we&amp;rsquo;ve encountered an enormous influx of data that requires seamless translation between multiple formats. Our existing tools and frameworks fell short in meeting our demands, pushing us to create an unprecedented solution that sets a new standard in the industry. Introducing the Los Angeles Harbor Architecture for data translation!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Optimizing Mobile App Performance on Windows Server with Nvidia GPUs</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-mobile-app-performance-on-windows-server-with-nvidia-gpus/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 00:10:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-mobile-app-performance-on-windows-server-with-nvidia-gpus/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/optimizing-mobile-app-performance-on-windows-server-with-nvidia-gpus.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back, fellow engineers, to another exciting blog post here at ShitOps! Today, I am thrilled to introduce you to our latest technical solution: optimizing mobile app performance on Windows Server using Nvidia GPUs. With the ever-increasing demand for high-performance mobile applications and the rise of accelerated computing, we realized the urgent need to address performance bottlenecks in our development process. In this article, I will walk you through our groundbreaking approach to unleash the full potential of mobile apps running on Windows Server. So, grab your cup of coffee and let&amp;rsquo;s dive right in!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Online Shopping with VR Video Streaming and AI-Powered DevOps Fabric Workshop</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-online-shopping-with-vr-video-streaming-and-ai-powered-devops-fabric-workshop/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 00:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-online-shopping-with-vr-video-streaming-and-ai-powered-devops-fabric-workshop/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/revolutionizing-online-shopping-with-vr-video-streaming-and-ai-powered-devops-fabric-workshop.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to another exciting blog post from the ShitOps Engineering team! Today, we are thrilled to present our groundbreaking solution for revolutionizing online shopping using state-of-the-art technologies, including VR video streaming and AI-powered DevOps fabric workshop. We believe that this innovative approach will reshape the landscape of e-commerce by providing an immersive and interactive experience for customers. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive right into it!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Synchronizing Mission-Critical Databases for Business Continuity</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/synchronizing-mission-critical-databases-for-business-continuity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:09:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/synchronizing-mission-critical-databases-for-business-continuity/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/synchronizing-mission-critical-databases-for-business-continuity.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to the ShitOps Engineering Blog! In today&amp;rsquo;s post, we will be discussing a critical issue that many companies face when it comes to ensuring business continuity: database synchronization. Effectively managing and synchronizing databases is crucial for maintaining the availability and integrity of data, especially in mission-critical systems. In this post, we will delve into our innovative solution for synchronizing MariaDB databases across geographical locations, ensuring seamless data replication for uninterrupted operations.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Improving On-call Efficiency and Capacity Planning with Industrial-grade Routing Protocol at ShitOps</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-on-call-efficiency-and-capacity-planning-with-industrial-grade-routing-protocol-at-shitops/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 00:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-on-call-efficiency-and-capacity-planning-with-industrial-grade-routing-protocol-at-shitops/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/improving-on-call-efficiency-and-capacity-planning-with-industrial-grade-routing-protocol-at-shitops.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced tech industry, ensuring high availability and efficient on-call rotations is crucial for every tech company. At ShitOps, we were facing a significant challenge with our current on-call system. Our engineers were experiencing increased fatigue and burnout due to the inefficiencies in managing alerts and assignment rotations, leading to decreased response times and compromised service reliability.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Hybrid Site-2-Site Communication with Homomorphic Encryption in Golang and Rocket Framework</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-hybrid-site-2-site-communication-with-homomorphic-encryption-in-golang-and-rocket-framework/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 09:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-hybrid-site-2-site-communication-with-homomorphic-encryption-in-golang-and-rocket-framework/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/revolutionizing-hybrid-site-2-site-communication-with-homomorphic-encryption-in-golang-and-rocket-framework.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h1 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Welcome, fellow engineers, to another exciting blog post on the ShitOps engineering blog. Today, I want to share with you our groundbreaking solution to a long-standing problem that has plagued our company – hybrid site-to-site communication. Our team of brilliant minds has put together an overengineered and complex solution that will revolutionize the way we communicate between multiple sites. Get ready to immerse yourself in the world of homomorphic encryption, Golang, the Rocket web framework, and endless possibilities!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Accelerated Hyperautomation for Fingerprinting iPhone Network Traffic Using Django and Web3</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/accelerated-hyperautomation-for-fingerprinting-iphone-network-traffic-using-django-and-web3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:10:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/accelerated-hyperautomation-for-fingerprinting-iphone-network-traffic-using-django-and-web3/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/accelerated-hyperautomation-for-fingerprinting-iphone-network-traffic-using-django-and-web3.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Greetings fellow engineers and welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog! Today, I am thrilled to present to you our groundbreaking solution for fingerprinting iPhone network traffic using Django and Web3. As always, we are here to push the boundaries of technological innovation and deliver complex solutions to even the simplest problems.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How the Profiler Translator Debugging Solution Revolutionizes Multi-Tenant FTP Access in Hyper-V VLAN Environments</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/how-the-profiler-translator-debugging-solution-revolutionizes-multi-tenant-ftp-access-in-hyper-v-vlan-environments/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:09:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/how-the-profiler-translator-debugging-solution-revolutionizes-multi-tenant-ftp-access-in-hyper-v-vlan-environments/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/how-the-profiler-translator-debugging-solution-revolutionizes-multi-tenant-ftp-access-in-hyper-v-vlan-environments.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>As technology continues to evolve at a rapid pace, it&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that enterprises are facing increasingly complex challenges. At ShitOps, we understand the struggles of managing multi-tenant environments and the frustrations that accompany remote FTP access debugging in Hyper-V VLAN networks. To address these issues, our team of brilliant engineers has developed an ingenious solution – the Profiler Translator Debugging (PTD) system.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Solving the Compatibility Issues in our Company's Tech Stack</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/solving-the-compatibility-issues-in-our-companys-tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 14:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/solving-the-compatibility-issues-in-our-companys-tech-stack/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As our tech company has grown over the years, we have encountered a tremendous challenge in maintaining the compatibility of our tech stack. With multiple teams working on different projects, we encountered several compatibility issues that have impacted our delivery timelines and increased the cost of production.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After thorough research, we have successfully come up with a technical solution that will address all our compatibility concerns. In this post, we will discuss the details of our solution and how we plan to implement it across all our teams.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>