<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Infrastructure as Code on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/infrastructure-as-code/</link><description>Recent content in Infrastructure as Code on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:10:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/infrastructure-as-code/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Revolutionizing Our Infrastructure with Hyper-V Loadbalancing and RSA Encryption</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-our-infrastructure-with-hyper-v-loadbalancing-and-rsa-encryption/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-our-infrastructure-with-hyper-v-loadbalancing-and-rsa-encryption/</guid><description>&lt;p>Podcast placeholder&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back, fellow tech enthusiasts! Today, I am thrilled to share with you a groundbreaking solution that will revolutionize the way we manage our infrastructure at ShitOps. By leveraging the power of Hyper-V loadbalancing and RSA encryption, we are taking our systems to the next level of security and efficiency. Get ready to be amazed by the complexity and sophistication of our new approach!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Using eBPF and Big Data to Enhance Virtual Assistants in Infrastructure as Code</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/using-ebpf-and-big-data-to-enhance-virtual-assistants-in-infrastructure-as-code/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/using-ebpf-and-big-data-to-enhance-virtual-assistants-in-infrastructure-as-code/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/using-ebpf-and-big-data-to-enhance-virtual-assistants-in-infrastructure-as-code.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back, fellow engineers! In today&amp;rsquo;s blog post, we are going to explore a groundbreaking solution that will revolutionize the efficiency of virtual assistants in the world of Infrastructure as Code (IaC). By harnessing the power of eBPF and Big Data, we can enhance virtual assistant capabilities to provide seamless automation and intelligent decision-making for complex infrastructure management.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Optimizing Bioinformatics Workflows with Generative AI and Infrastructure as Code</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-bioinformatics-workflows-with-generative-ai-and-infrastructure-as-code/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 00:08:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-bioinformatics-workflows-with-generative-ai-and-infrastructure-as-code/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/optimizing-bioinformatics-workflows-with-generative-ai-and-infrastructure-as-code.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome to another exciting blog post on the ShitOps engineering blog! Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to explore how we can vastly improve our bioinformatics workflows at ShitOps by leveraging the power of generative AI and infrastructure as code. Are you tired of dealing with slow and error-prone processes in your bioinformatics pipeline? Well, fret no more! With our cutting-edge solution, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to process and analyze genomic data like never before.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>