<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Password Security on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/password-security/</link><description>Recent content in Password Security on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:09:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/password-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Revolutionizing Password Security with Explainable AI and Rest API</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-password-security-with-explainable-ai-and-rest-api/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:09:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-password-security-with-explainable-ai-and-rest-api/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog! Today, we are diving into a groundbreaking solution to the age-old problem of password security. As we all know, passwords are the first line of defense in protecting our systems from malicious attacks. However, traditional password policies are often weak and vulnerable to breaches. But fear not, for we have developed a state-of-the-art system that leverages Explainable Artificial Intelligence (XAI) and Rest APIs to revolutionize password security across the tech industry.</description></item><item><title>Enhancing Password Security in Azure using VMware Tanzu Kubernetes</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/enhancing-password-security-in-azure-using-vmware-tanzu-kubernetes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:09:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/enhancing-password-security-in-azure-using-vmware-tanzu-kubernetes/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, tech enthusiasts! In this blog post, we are going to tackle a critical problem that every tech company faces: password security. We all know that passwords are the gatekeepers of our digital assets, and it is paramount to ensure their utmost security. At ShitOps, our team of elite engineers has come up with an innovative solution to enhance password security in Azure using the power of VMware Tanzu Kubernetes.</description></item></channel></rss>