<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Engineering on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/engineering/</link><description>Recent content in Engineering on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 21:51:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Hyper-Optimized Solution for Our Server Room Cooling Problem</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/the-hyper-optimized-solution-for-our-server-room-cooling-problem/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 21:51:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/the-hyper-optimized-solution-for-our-server-room-cooling-problem/</guid><description>Introduction At our company, we have been facing a major challenge in our server room. Our servers generate a lot of heat and require a consistent temperature to function optimally. The current cooling solution, which involves traditional air conditioning units, is not meeting our needs. We have tried various solutions, including installing additional AC units and fans, but none of them seem to be effective. After thorough research and analysis, I came up with an innovative solution to solve our cooling problem.</description></item><item><title>The Unstoppable Spam: A Technical Solution</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/the-unstoppable-spam/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 21:47:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/the-unstoppable-spam/</guid><description>Introduction Spam has been a problem for as long as the internet has existed. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s email spam, forum spam, or social media spam, it&amp;rsquo;s a constant annoyance that has only gotten worse over time. Our company, like many others, has been struggling to combat spam on our platform. We&amp;rsquo;ve tried various solutions, from CAPTCHAs to machine learning algorithms, but nothing seems to work. That&amp;rsquo;s why we&amp;rsquo;ve come up with a new, revolutionary approach: the Unstoppable Spam Filter.</description></item><item><title>The Optimal Temperature Control System for Our Data Centers</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/the-optimal-temperature-control-system-for-our-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 21:44:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/the-optimal-temperature-control-system-for-our-data-centers/</guid><description>Introduction As an industry leader in cloud computing, our company operates multiple data centers around the world. In order to maintain the optimal performance of our servers and ensure the reliability of our services, we must carefully control the temperature of our data centers. However, this is a complex problem that requires a sophisticated solution. In this post, we will explore our approach to developing an optimal temperature control system for our data centers.</description></item><item><title>Optimizing Data Processing with a Multi-layered Pipeline</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-data-processing-with-a-multi-layered-pipeline/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 21:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-data-processing-with-a-multi-layered-pipeline/</guid><description>Introduction Data processing is a critical component of any tech company. As a team lead in charge of data management at my company, I have been constantly seeking ways to optimize our existing data pipeline. Our recent growth has led to an increase in data volume and complexity, making it even more necessary to develop a robust pipeline that can handle the changes effectively.
Our existing data pipeline has multiple layers for processing and analyzing data.</description></item></channel></rss>