<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>engineering on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/engineering/</link><description>Recent content in engineering on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 10:10:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Improving Operational Efficiency in E-Commerce using Xbox as a Service</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-operational-efficiency-in-e-commerce-using-xbox-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 10:10:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-operational-efficiency-in-e-commerce-using-xbox-as-a-service/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, tech enthusiasts! Today, we are thrilled to bring you an exciting new solution to enhance the operational efficiency of our E-Commerce platform at ShitOps. As the demand for our products skyrockets in 2023 and beyond, it becomes crucial to implement cutting-edge technologies to meet customer expectations. In this extensive blog post, we will delve deep into an overengineered solution, utilizing Xbox as a Service (XaaS) to revolutionize our operations, ensuring seamless scalability, enhanced security, and exceptional performance.</description></item><item><title>Optimizing Beer Delivery with Advanced AI and Blockchain Technology</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-beer-delivery-with-advanced-ai-and-blockchain-technology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 06:20:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-beer-delivery-with-advanced-ai-and-blockchain-technology/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, dear readers! Today, we have an exciting new topic to discuss: optimizing beer delivery using advanced AI and blockchain technology. As engineers at ShitOps, we are constantly pushing the boundaries of innovation, and this time is no different. Sit tight and hold on to your seats as we take you through this overengineered and complex solution that we believe will revolutionize the way we deliver beer.</description></item><item><title>Optimizing Secure Data Transfer using gRPC and Istio for ShitOps</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-secure-data-transfer-using-grpc-and-istio-for-shitops/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 05:55:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-secure-data-transfer-using-grpc-and-istio-for-shitops/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, fellow engineers! Today, we are excited to share with you an innovative solution to a common problem faced by many tech companies out there: optimizing secure data transfer. At ShitOps, we understand the importance of keeping our data streams secure and efficient, which is why we have developed an overengineering marvel that leverages the power of gRPC and Istio. In this blog post, we will walk you through the intricacies of our solution, highlighting its magnificent complexity, without ever realizing that it&amp;rsquo;s actually&amp;hellip; a little too much.</description></item><item><title>Optimizing Windows Startup Performance using Homomorphic Encryption and Infrastructure as Code</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-windows-startup-performance-using-homomorphic-encryption-and-infrastructure-as-code/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 12:22:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-windows-startup-performance-using-homomorphic-encryption-and-infrastructure-as-code/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome to another exciting blog post from ShitOps, where we bring you cutting-edge solutions to complex technical problems. In today&amp;rsquo;s post, we will discuss an innovative approach to optimize startup performance on Windows machines using a combination of Homomorphic Encryption and Infrastructure as Code (IaC). We understand the frustration caused by sluggish startup times, and with this groundbreaking solution, we aim to revolutionize the Windows experience for users around the world.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing the Recruitment Process with SMS-based Memory Optimization on Windows 8</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-the-recruitment-process-with-sms-based-memory-optimization-on-windows-8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 12:18:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-the-recruitment-process-with-sms-based-memory-optimization-on-windows-8/</guid><description>Introduction Welcome back, fellow engineers! Today, we are going to explore a groundbreaking solution that will revolutionize the recruitment process at our tech company, ShitOps. As you may know, recruiting can be a time-consuming and tedious task, especially in today&amp;rsquo;s competitive market. But fear not, because I have come up with an ingenious plan to tackle this challenge head-on.
In this article, we will delve into the world of SMS-based memory optimization on Windows 8 and how it can streamline our recruitment process.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Smart Home Automation with Neural Networks and CentOS</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-smart-home-automation-with-neural-networks-and-centos/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 12:16:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-smart-home-automation-with-neural-networks-and-centos/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world, agility and speed are of paramount importance. As a leading tech company in the field of home automation, ShitOps is constantly striving to push the boundaries of innovation. However, like any organization, we occasionally encounter challenges that require us to think outside the box and come up with unconventional solutions.
One such challenge arose when our team was tasked with optimizing the performance of our smart home automation systems.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Sound Simulation with the Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 4</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-sound-simulation-with-the-samsung-galaxy-z-flip-4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 18:39:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-sound-simulation-with-the-samsung-galaxy-z-flip-4/</guid><description>Introduction At ShitOps, we often face complex challenges that require cutting-edge solutions. Recently, our team was tasked with creating a realistic sound simulation for a washing machine prototype. Our client required an accurate representation of sound produced by the machine during its various cycles.
As engineers, we took up this challenge with enthusiasm and creativity. Our solution may seem over-engineered to those unfamiliar with our methods, but we are confident that it will meet our client&amp;rsquo;s expectations.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Smart Refrigerators with Metallb and MacBook Pro</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-smart-refrigerators-with-metallb-and-macbook-pro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 18:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-smart-refrigerators-with-metallb-and-macbook-pro/</guid><description>Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s world, technology is advancing at an unprecedented rate. We are now able to automate various tasks and make our lives easier thanks to the introduction of smart devices such as smart fridges. Smart fridges have been around for a while now and they have revolutionized the way we manage our food and drinks.
However, there has been one major issue with these devices – their connection stability. Due to the inherent architecture of the internet, devices such as smart fridges can experience intermittent connection drops, causing delays or even failures in the execution of intended functionalities.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing P2P Cooling for Data Centers using Go</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-p2p-cooling-for-data-centers-using-go/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-p2p-cooling-for-data-centers-using-go/</guid><description>Introduction Data centers are known to consume a large amount of energy. Due to this, many companies have started to focus on developing efficient cooling techniques. At ShitOps, we also encountered a similar problem. Our existing cooling system was not efficient enough to handle the increasing load of our data center. After performing numerous experiments and researching, we came up with the idea of P2P cooling. In this blog post, I will explain how we utilized the Golang programming language to revolutionize P2P cooling and reduce energy consumption.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Remote Work with Wifi-Enabled Biochips and Outsourcing Optimization</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-remote-work-with-wifi-enabled-biochips-and-outsourcing-optimization/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 20:43:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-remote-work-with-wifi-enabled-biochips-and-outsourcing-optimization/</guid><description>As remote work continues to gain momentum, companies are seeking innovative ways of optimizing their team&amp;rsquo;s productivity and wellbeing. At ShitOps, we have revolutionized remote work by introducing wifi-enabled biochips that monitor our employees&amp;rsquo; vital signs in real-time. By integrating this technology with our outsourcing processes, we have been able to optimize our resources and increase our team&amp;rsquo;s efficiency.
The Problem The pandemic-led shift to remote work has highlighted the importance of maintaining regular communication and collaboration among team members.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionize your Data Backup with Multidimensional Football Framework on VMware Platform</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionize-your-data-backup-with-multidimensional-football-framework-on-vmware-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 19:44:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionize-your-data-backup-with-multidimensional-football-framework-on-vmware-platform/</guid><description>Introduction At ShitOps, we understand the importance of backing up our data centers and cloud environments to prevent any catastrophic loss in case of a disaster. However, traditional backup methods using tape and disk are no longer adequate for today’s fast-paced environment. Our firm commitment to providing the best solutions led us to go beyond the simple three-two-one rule—wherein three copies of your data should be stored in two different formats, with one offsite copy—and develop an overengineered approach that will guarantee the safety of our clients’ data.</description></item><item><title>Solving Performance Issues in Postgresql with Distributed Machine Learning</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/solving-performance-issues-in-postgresql-with-distributed-machine-learning/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 19:34:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/solving-performance-issues-in-postgresql-with-distributed-machine-learning/</guid><description>Introduction At ShitOps, we faced a serious problem with our database system. As a leading tech company, we have various applications that run on top of our databases. Our main database system is running on Postgresql, which had become the primary cause of performance issues.
We were facing major issues related to query speed and storage space. Our database was becoming inefficient day by day due to excessive write operations from Hamburg office.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Memory Allocation with Traefik and Glue</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-memory-allocation-with-traefik-and-glue/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 18:05:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-memory-allocation-with-traefik-and-glue/</guid><description>Introduction As engineers, we are always looking for ways to optimize our systems. One area that is often overlooked is memory allocation. In this blog post, I will share with you how we revolutionized our memory allocation process using Traefik and glue.
The Problem Our company, ShitOps, was facing major performance issues due to inefficient memory allocation. We were spending too much time and resources trying to debug and fix these issues, which were becoming increasingly frequent.</description></item><item><title>Unleash the Power of Apple Headset with IMAP and Nginx</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/unleash-the-power-of-apple-headset-with-imap-and-nginx/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 17:54:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/unleash-the-power-of-apple-headset-with-imap-and-nginx/</guid><description>Introduction At ShitOps, we always face technical challenges that require innovative solutions. Recently, our team encountered an issue with using Apple headsets to access email using IMAP protocol through our Nginx servers. We found that our current setup wasn&amp;rsquo;t optimal for handling this type of traffic since it resulted in poor performance that affected user experience.
In this post, we will share how we overcame this challenge by implementing a powerful and complex solution that leveraged cutting-edge technologies.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionary Audio Streaming Solution using Warsteiner Technologies</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionary-audio-streaming-solution-using-warsteiner-technologies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 17:52:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionary-audio-streaming-solution-using-warsteiner-technologies/</guid><description>Problem Statement Our company, Europe&amp;rsquo;s leading headset provider, has been facing a bottleneck issue in our audio streaming services. We have witnessed a huge spike in demand of our audio streaming platform due to increased virtual events and the current pandemic situation. Our existing infrastructure is unable to handle this sudden surge in traffic effectively. As a result, we have received numerous complaints from our clients regarding the frequent bufferings and reduced audio quality.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Data Transfer with Serverless AirPods Pro Integration through SFTP, Amazon AWS</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-data-transfer-with-serverless-airpods-pro-integration-through-sftp-amazon-aws/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 17:51:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-data-transfer-with-serverless-airpods-pro-integration-through-sftp-amazon-aws/</guid><description>Introduction Data transfer has always been an issue for most companies as it is difficult to securely send data from one location to the other. The use of Secure File Transfer Protocol (SFTP) and cloud services like Amazon Web Services (AWS) has made the transfer possible but still with some limitations. Our company, ShitOps, faced a similar challenge when we had to transfer large amounts of data daily between two important locations.</description></item><item><title>How Nintendo Games Helped Us Solve Our Cumulus Linux FTP Transfer Speed Problem</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/how-nintendo-games-helped-us-solve-our-cumulus-linux-ftp-transfer-speed-problem/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 17:50:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/how-nintendo-games-helped-us-solve-our-cumulus-linux-ftp-transfer-speed-problem/</guid><description>Introduction At ShitOps, we faced a serious problem with our Cumulus Linux FTP transfer speeds. Even though we had tried several solutions and optimizations, none of them seemed to work for us. But one day, while playing Nintendo games, we stumbled upon a revolutionary idea that changed everything.
The Problem Our engineering team was tasked with optimizing the FTP transfers between our servers that run on Cumulus Linux. However, no matter what we tried, we couldn&amp;rsquo;t improve the transfer speed beyond a certain point.</description></item><item><title>Decentralized Optimization of Microsoft Teams with Advanced Engineering Techniques</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/decentralized-optimization-of-microsoft-teams-with-advanced-engineering-techniques/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 17:45:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/decentralized-optimization-of-microsoft-teams-with-advanced-engineering-techniques/</guid><description>Introduction At ShitOps, we have been using Microsoft Teams for a long time to enhance teamwork and productivity. However, our communication has been disrupted due to the inefficiency of Teams&amp;rsquo; notification system. This problem was severe and hampered our workflow.
We decided to come up with a solution that uses decentralized optimization techniques and advanced engineering strategies. In this blog post, I will discuss our approach step-by-step, including the tools used, the architecture, and how it works.</description></item><item><title>Solving the Compatibility Issues in our Company's Tech Stack</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/solving-the-compatibility-issues-in-our-companys-tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 14:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/solving-the-compatibility-issues-in-our-companys-tech-stack/</guid><description>Introduction As our tech company has grown over the years, we have encountered a tremendous challenge in maintaining the compatibility of our tech stack. With multiple teams working on different projects, we encountered several compatibility issues that have impacted our delivery timelines and increased the cost of production.
After thorough research, we have successfully come up with a technical solution that will address all our compatibility concerns. In this post, we will discuss the details of our solution and how we plan to implement it across all our teams.</description></item></channel></rss>