<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nintendo DS on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/nintendo-ds/</link><description>Recent content in Nintendo DS on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 00:10:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/nintendo-ds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enhancing Time-Sensitive Intrusion Prevention with IoT: A Revolutionary Approach</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/enhancing-time-sensitive-intrusion-prevention-with-iot/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/enhancing-time-sensitive-intrusion-prevention-with-iot/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Greetings, fellow engineers! Today, I am thrilled to share with you an innovative solution that will revolutionize the way we approach time-sensitive intrusion prevention using IoT. Our cutting-edge approach incorporates advanced technologies such as the Nintendo DS, 4K resolution, and the concept of a metaverse. Get ready to be blown away by the complexity and uniqueness of this solution!
The Problem At ShitOps, we strive for the highest levels of security and operational excellence.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Loadbalancing with Nintendo DS and Headphones</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-loadbalancing-with-nintendo-ds-and-headphones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:07:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-loadbalancing-with-nintendo-ds-and-headphones/</guid><description>Introduction As our company grew in size, we found that our Windows Server-based loadbalancing solution was no longer efficient enough to serve our customer&amp;rsquo;s requests. We needed to find a new solution, but with so many options available, it was difficult to make the right choice.
After spending countless hours brainstorming and experimenting with different ideas, we finally struck upon a unique solution; what if we could employ Nintendo DS consoles, coupled with headphones, for a state of the art load balancing solution?</description></item></channel></rss>