<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Configuration Management on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/configuration-management/</link><description>Recent content in Configuration Management on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 08:08:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/configuration-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Optimizing Configuration Management with Out of Band nmap Scans in Australia</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-configuration-management-with-out-of-band-nmap-scans-in-australia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 08:08:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-configuration-management-with-out-of-band-nmap-scans-in-australia/</guid><description>Introduction Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog, where we dive deep into the world of tech solutions for complex problems. Today, we are going to discuss how we can optimize our configuration management process by leveraging out of band nmap scans in Australia.
The Problem Imagine this scenario: your company has just expanded its operations to multiple locations across Australia, and you are responsible for managing the configurations of all the devices in these locations.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Configuration Management with Quantum Supremacy</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-configuration-management-with-quantum-supremacy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 00:09:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-configuration-management-with-quantum-supremacy/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog, where we constantly push the boundaries of technology to solve the most complex problems in the industry. In this post, we will discuss how we are revolutionizing configuration management using the power of Quantum Supremacy.
The Problem At ShitOps, we have been facing a significant challenge with our current configuration management system. Our legacy system, built on Windows XP and PostgreSQL, has become increasingly unreliable and difficult to maintain.</description></item><item><title>How Blockchain-powered, AI-driven Cybersecurity Can Revolutionize DNS Resolver Performance</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/how-blockchain-powered-ai-driven-cybersecurity-can-revolutionize-dns-resolver-performance/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/how-blockchain-powered-ai-driven-cybersecurity-can-revolutionize-dns-resolver-performance/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, fellow tech enthusiasts! Today, we are taking a deep dive into the world of cybersecurity and exploring how blockchain technology coupled with artificial intelligence can revolutionize the performance of DNS resolvers. You might be wondering, why do we need such a solution? Well, let me walk you through the problem and present you with our groundbreaking, state-of-the-art solution.
The Problem: Packet Loss in DNS Resolution In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced digital world, every millisecond counts.</description></item></channel></rss>