<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Green Technology on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/green-technology/</link><description>Recent content in Green Technology on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:10:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/green-technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Revolutionizing Green Telemetry Solutions with Extreme Programming in Windows 11 for 2021</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-green-telemetry-solutions-with-extreme-programming-in-windows-11-for-2021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:10:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-green-telemetry-solutions-with-extreme-programming-in-windows-11-for-2021/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog, where we constantly strive to push the boundaries of technology and innovation. In this post, we will be diving into our latest project that aims to revolutionize Green Telemetry solutions using Extreme Programming principles on the newly released Windows 11 platform.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-problem-statement">The Problem Statement&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In the ever-evolving landscape of technology, it has become increasingly crucial for companies to monitor their systems&amp;rsquo; environmental impact. As a leading tech company, ShitOps is committed to reducing our carbon footprint and implementing sustainable practices across all our operations. However, we are facing a major challenge in accurately capturing and analyzing real-time telemetry data from our various servers running on CentOS.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Electricity Consumption with Green Technology and GPS Tracking</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-electricity-consumption-with-green-technology-and-gps-tracking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:08:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-electricity-consumption-with-green-technology-and-gps-tracking/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/revolutionizing-electricity-consumption-with-green-technology-and-gps-tracking.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back, fellow engineers and tech enthusiasts! In today&amp;rsquo;s blog post, we are thrilled to unveil an innovative solution revolutionizing electricity consumption in the modern world. Drawing inspiration from cutting-edge green technology and harnessing the power of GPS tracking, we have developed an ultra-clever system to optimize energy usage. Prepare to be amazed as we delve into the depths of this groundbreaking implementation!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Increasing Availability and Performance with Green Technology in the ShitOps Office</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/increasing-availability-and-performance-with-green-technology-in-the-shitops-office/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/increasing-availability-and-performance-with-green-technology-in-the-shitops-office/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/increasing-availability-and-performance-with-green-technology-in-the-shitops-office.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back, fellow tech enthusiasts, to another exciting blog post on the engineering marvels happening at ShitOps! Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll be discussing how we tackled a major problem affecting our office&amp;rsquo;s availability and performance by leveraging cutting-edge green technology. This innovation has not only revolutionized our operations but also paved the way for a greener tomorrow. So without further ado, let&amp;rsquo;s dive into this technological masterpiece!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>