<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Microservices on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/microservices/</link><description>Recent content in Microservices on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:11:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/microservices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Revolutionizing Fingerprinting in Event-Driven Microservices with Sway 2.0</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-fingerprinting-in-event-driven-microservices-with-sway-20/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-fingerprinting-in-event-driven-microservices-with-sway-20/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/revolutionizing-fingerprinting-in-event-driven-microservices-with-sway-20.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back, engineers, to another exciting blog post from the tech wizards at ShitOps! Today, we are going to delve into the world of fingerprinting in event-driven microservices. We all know how crucial it is to accurately identify and track events within our systems, but traditional methods of fingerprinting just aren&amp;rsquo;t cutting it anymore. That&amp;rsquo;s where Sway 2.0 comes in.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Optimizing Data Processing in ShitOps: A Groundbreaking Solution</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-data-processing-in-shitops/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:09:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-data-processing-in-shitops/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/optimizing-data-processing-in-shitops.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Greetings, fellow engineers! Today, I am thrilled to unveil an innovative solution we have developed at ShitOps to optimize our data processing pipeline. At the heart of our operations lies a pressing challenge: the need for high-speed and efficient data ingestion and analysis. In this blog post, we will dive deep into the technical details of our groundbreaking approach that leverages cutting-edge technologies and extravagant complexities.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Building a Highly Scalable and Resilient Microservices Architecture with Istio and NixOS</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/building-a-highly-scalable-and-resilient-microservices-architecture-with-istio-and-nixos/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:09:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/building-a-highly-scalable-and-resilient-microservices-architecture-with-istio-and-nixos/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/building-a-highly-scalable-and-resilient-microservices-architecture-with-istio-and-nixos.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to another exciting post on the ShitOps engineering blog! Today, I am thrilled to discuss a technical solution that will take your company&amp;rsquo;s infrastructure to new heights of scalability and resiliency. We often find ourselves facing challenges in our day-to-day operations that require dynamic and robust solutions. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through our journey of building a highly scalable and resilient microservices architecture using cutting-edge technologies like Istio and NixOS.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Optimizing Music Delivery in a Microservices Architecture</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-music-delivery-in-a-microservices-architecture/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:10:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-music-delivery-in-a-microservices-architecture/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog! Today, we are thrilled to present our latest technical solution to optimize music delivery in our microservices architecture. As we all know, music is an integral part of our lives and has become even more important with the advent of streaming platforms. However, ensuring a seamless and uninterrupted music listening experience can be quite challenging, especially when dealing with millions of users concurrently accessing our platform. In this post, we will explore how we leveraged cutting-edge technologies to revolutionize music delivery at ShitOps, making it faster, more reliable, and more enjoyable for our users.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Optimizing Microservices with Blockchain to Streamline Hamburger Production</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-microservices-with-blockchain-to-streamline-hamburger-production/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 17:53:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-microservices-with-blockchain-to-streamline-hamburger-production/</guid><description>&lt;p>As a leading tech company in the hamburger industry, we at ShitOps take pride in delivering high-quality and delicious hamburgers to our customers. However, we&amp;rsquo;ve encountered a major problem that has been plaguing our production process for far too long: Inefficient microservices that fail to communicate properly.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The problem arose when we started using microservices to streamline our production process. Initially, we thought it would be an excellent idea as it would help us break down our application into smaller, more manageable pieces. But as time went on, we noticed that the microservices were not communicating with each other properly. This resulted in longer production times, more errors, and ultimately, dissatisfied customers.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>