<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>microservices on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/microservices/</link><description>Recent content in microservices on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:10:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/microservices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Optimizing Music Delivery in a Microservices Architecture</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-music-delivery-in-a-microservices-architecture/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:10:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-music-delivery-in-a-microservices-architecture/</guid><description>Introduction Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog! Today, we are thrilled to present our latest technical solution to optimize music delivery in our microservices architecture. As we all know, music is an integral part of our lives and has become even more important with the advent of streaming platforms. However, ensuring a seamless and uninterrupted music listening experience can be quite challenging, especially when dealing with millions of users concurrently accessing our platform.</description></item><item><title>Optimizing Microservices with Blockchain to Streamline Hamburger Production</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-microservices-with-blockchain-to-streamline-hamburger-production/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 17:53:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-microservices-with-blockchain-to-streamline-hamburger-production/</guid><description>As a leading tech company in the hamburger industry, we at ShitOps take pride in delivering high-quality and delicious hamburgers to our customers. However, we&amp;rsquo;ve encountered a major problem that has been plaguing our production process for far too long: Inefficient microservices that fail to communicate properly.
The problem arose when we started using microservices to streamline our production process. Initially, we thought it would be an excellent idea as it would help us break down our application into smaller, more manageable pieces.</description></item></channel></rss>