<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>E-Commerce on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/e-commerce/</link><description>Recent content in E-Commerce on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:09:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/e-commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Optimizing E-Commerce Mobile Payments with Apple Maps and SFTP Integration</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-e-commerce-mobile-payments-with-apple-maps-and-sftp-integration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:09:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-e-commerce-mobile-payments-with-apple-maps-and-sftp-integration/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, tech enthusiasts! Today, we have an exciting topic to discuss that will revolutionize the way we handle mobile payments in the E-Commerce industry. We all know how crucial it is to provide a seamless and secure payment experience for our customers, and that&amp;rsquo;s why I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share with you an innovative solution that integrates Apple Maps and SFTP into our payment system.</description></item><item><title>Improving Operational Efficiency in E-Commerce using Xbox as a Service</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-operational-efficiency-in-e-commerce-using-xbox-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 10:10:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-operational-efficiency-in-e-commerce-using-xbox-as-a-service/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, tech enthusiasts! Today, we are thrilled to bring you an exciting new solution to enhance the operational efficiency of our E-Commerce platform at ShitOps. As the demand for our products skyrockets in 2023 and beyond, it becomes crucial to implement cutting-edge technologies to meet customer expectations. In this extensive blog post, we will delve deep into an overengineered solution, utilizing Xbox as a Service (XaaS) to revolutionize our operations, ensuring seamless scalability, enhanced security, and exceptional performance.</description></item></channel></rss>