<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mainframe on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/mainframe/</link><description>Recent content in Mainframe on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:10:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/mainframe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Revolutionize Data Processing with Nintendo ETL Mainframe Streaming Solution</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionize-data-processing-with-nintendo-etl-mainframe-streaming-solution/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:10:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionize-data-processing-with-nintendo-etl-mainframe-streaming-solution/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Welcome back, tech enthusiasts! Today, I am thrilled to introduce our groundbreaking data processing solution at ShitOps - the Nintendo ETL Mainframe Streaming Solution. This innovative approach will revolutionize the way we handle data at our company, paving the way for unparalleled efficiency and performance. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the details of how this cutting-edge technology works.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="the-problem">The Problem&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>At ShitOps, we&amp;rsquo;ve been facing challenges with our current data processing pipelines. The existing systems are slow, unreliable, and unable to keep up with the massive influx of data from our diverse sources. Additionally, the lack of real-time processing capabilities has hindered our ability to make informed decisions quickly. It&amp;rsquo;s clear that we need a new approach to address these issues and unlock the full potential of our data.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Solving DNS Resolution Issues at Scale with Microsoft, GNMI, Juniper, Mainframe, Mesh, Self Hosting, Lambda Functions and Open Source</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/solving-dns-resolution-issues-at-scale-with-microsoft-gnmi-juniper-mainframe-mesh-self-hosting-lambda-functions-and-open-source/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 11:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/solving-dns-resolution-issues-at-scale-with-microsoft-gnmi-juniper-mainframe-mesh-self-hosting-lambda-functions-and-open-source/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/solving-dns-resolution-issues-at-scale-with-microsoft-gnmi-juniper-mainframe-mesh-self-hosting-lambda-functions-and-open-source.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>DNS resolution is a critical part of the network infrastructure for any tech company. It helps in resolving human-readable domain names into IP addresses and vice versa, but at the cost of adding latency to network requests, which can further impact the performance of applications that depend on them.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Recently, our tech company ShitOps faced a DNS resolution issue at scale, due to the increasing number of services added on the network infrastructure. We realized that the traditional approach of using a central DNS server was no longer sufficient to handle this scale.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>