<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Microsoft Azure on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/microsoft-azure/</link><description>Recent content in Microsoft Azure on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:11:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/microsoft-azure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Revolutionizing Real-Time Fridge Monitoring with Microsoft Azure and Vue.js</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-real-time-fridge-monitoring-with-microsoft-azure-and-vuejs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:11:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-real-time-fridge-monitoring-with-microsoft-azure-and-vuejs/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/revolutionizing-real-time-fridge-monitoring-with-microsoft-azure-and-vuejs.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog, where we tackle the most pressing challenges in the world of technology. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re diving into the exciting world of fridge monitoring and how we are revolutionizing it with the power of Microsoft Azure and Vue.js.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-problem">The Problem&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for companies to have real-time visibility into the status of their fridges. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s monitoring temperature, inventory levels, or maintenance schedules, having accurate and up-to-date information is key to ensuring smooth operations. However, our current fridge monitoring system is outdated and inefficient. It lacks the scalability and flexibility needed to keep up with our rapidly expanding operations. We need a solution that can handle a distributed network of fridges across multiple locations, provide real-time updates, and integrate seamlessly with our existing infrastructure.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>