<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Headphones on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/headphones/</link><description>Recent content in Headphones on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:08:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/headphones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Revolutionary Approach to Optimizing Swarm Robotics with Headphones</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/a-revolutionary-approach-to-optimizing-swarm-robotics-with-headphones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:08:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/a-revolutionary-approach-to-optimizing-swarm-robotics-with-headphones/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/a-revolutionary-approach-to-optimizing-swarm-robotics-with-headphones.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to another exciting blog post from the engineering team at ShitOps! Today, we are thrilled to present a revolutionary approach to optimizing swarm robotics using headphones. Yes, you heard it right, headphones! In this article, we will explore how this unlikely combination can enhance the efficiency and effectiveness of swarm robotics in ways you never thought possible. So grab your coffee, put on your headphones, and let&amp;rsquo;s dive in!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Loadbalancing with Nintendo DS and Headphones</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-loadbalancing-with-nintendo-ds-and-headphones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:07:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-loadbalancing-with-nintendo-ds-and-headphones/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As our company grew in size, we found that our Windows Server-based loadbalancing solution was no longer efficient enough to serve our customer&amp;rsquo;s requests. We needed to find a new solution, but with so many options available, it was difficult to make the right choice.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After spending countless hours brainstorming and experimenting with different ideas, we finally struck upon a unique solution; what if we could employ Nintendo DS consoles, coupled with headphones, for a state of the art load balancing solution? And what if we told you that we&amp;rsquo;ve managed to incorporate lambda functions and embedded these Nintendo DS consoles into our server network?&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>