<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Web4 on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/web4/</link><description>Recent content in Web4 on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:12:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/web4/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Revolutionizing Cybersecurity with Web4 Headphones</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-cybersecurity-with-web4-headphones/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-cybersecurity-with-web4-headphones/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/revolutionizing-cybersecurity-with-web4-headphones.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back, dear readers, to another exciting blog post from the tech wizards at ShitOps! Today, we are going to delve into the groundbreaking world of cybersecurity and how we are revolutionizing it with the power of Web4 headphones.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-problem">The Problem&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In the fast-paced world of technology, cybersecurity has become more important than ever. With the rise of IoT devices, cloud computing, and interconnected systems, the attack surface for malicious actors has expanded exponentially. Traditional cybersecurity measures such as firewalls and antivirus software are no longer enough to protect our sensitive data and networks. We needed a solution that could adapt to the ever-evolving threat landscape and provide real-time protection against advanced cyber threats.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Backend Architecture with Azure Web4 and Istio</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-backend-architecture-with-azure-web4-and-istio/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:12:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-backend-architecture-with-azure-web4-and-istio/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog! Today, we are going to delve into a revolutionary approach to backend architecture using the power of Azure Web4 and Istio.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-problem-statement">The Problem Statement&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Imagine a scenario where our backend services are running on traditional servers, accessing data stored in relational databases. We have been facing issues with scalability, high latency, and lack of resilience. Additionally, ensuring secure communication between services has been a challenge. Our team has been brainstorming ways to address these issues and elevate our backend architecture to the next level.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>