<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Streaming on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/streaming/</link><description>Recent content in Streaming on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:10:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/streaming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Revolutionize Data Processing with Nintendo ETL Mainframe Streaming Solution</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionize-data-processing-with-nintendo-etl-mainframe-streaming-solution/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:10:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionize-data-processing-with-nintendo-etl-mainframe-streaming-solution/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Welcome back, tech enthusiasts! Today, I am thrilled to introduce our groundbreaking data processing solution at ShitOps - the Nintendo ETL Mainframe Streaming Solution. This innovative approach will revolutionize the way we handle data at our company, paving the way for unparalleled efficiency and performance. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the details of how this cutting-edge technology works.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="the-problem">The Problem&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>At ShitOps, we&amp;rsquo;ve been facing challenges with our current data processing pipelines. The existing systems are slow, unreliable, and unable to keep up with the massive influx of data from our diverse sources. Additionally, the lack of real-time processing capabilities has hindered our ability to make informed decisions quickly. It&amp;rsquo;s clear that we need a new approach to address these issues and unlock the full potential of our data.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Security with Hyper-V Streaming Technology</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-security-with-hyper-v-streaming-technology/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 19:13:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-security-with-hyper-v-streaming-technology/</guid><description>&lt;p>As a leading tech company in the security industry, we are always striving to improve our products and stay ahead of our competitors. Recently, we encountered a problem that threatened the security of our entire system. It all started when an employee lost their Casio G-Shock Watch, which contained sensitive data about the company on its built-in iPhone app. Although the phone was password protected, we knew that if it fell into the wrong hands, access to our secure network could be compromised.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>