<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Postgresql on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/postgresql/</link><description>Recent content in Postgresql on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:14:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/postgresql/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Revolutionizing Headphone Usage with AI and PostgreSQL</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-headphone-usage-with-ai-and-postgresql/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:14:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-headphone-usage-with-ai-and-postgresql/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Greetings, fellow engineers! Today, I am thrilled to share with you a groundbreaking solution that will revolutionize the way we use headphones at ShitOps. By leveraging the power of Artificial Intelligence (AI) and the robustness of PostgreSQL, we have developed a cutting-edge system that will completely transform how we interact with our audio devices.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-problem-statement">The Problem Statement&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>At ShitOps, we have encountered a common issue among our employees who use headphones during work hours. Often, they face difficulties in managing multiple audio sources simultaneously. This leads to confusion and frustration, ultimately impacting their productivity. As a tech-savvy company, we knew there had to be a smarter, more efficient way to handle this challenge.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Solving Performance Issues in Postgresql with Distributed Machine Learning</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/solving-performance-issues-in-postgresql-with-distributed-machine-learning/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 19:34:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/solving-performance-issues-in-postgresql-with-distributed-machine-learning/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>At ShitOps, we faced a serious problem with our database system. As a leading tech company, we have various applications that run on top of our databases. Our main database system is running on Postgresql, which had become the primary cause of performance issues.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We were facing major issues related to query speed and storage space. Our database was becoming inefficient day by day due to excessive write operations from Hamburg office. The problem emerged when we noticed that our lazy replica was getting outdated faster than usual because queries took longer to execute on it compared to the master node.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>