<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sftp on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/sftp/</link><description>Recent content in Sftp on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 00:09:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/sftp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Optimizing TCP Performance with Version Control and Virtual Machines</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-tcp-performance-with-version-control-and-virtual-machines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 00:09:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-tcp-performance-with-version-control-and-virtual-machines/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/optimizing-tcp-performance-with-version-control-and-virtual-machines.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h1 id="optimizing-tcp-performance-with-version-control-and-virtual-machines">Optimizing TCP Performance with Version Control and Virtual Machines&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to another exciting post on the ShitOps engineering blog, where we dive deep into all things tech and explore groundbreaking solutions that are sure to revolutionize the industry. Today, we will tackle a pressing problem faced by our company—suboptimal TCP performance—and present an innovative solution that will undoubtedly blow your mind.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Data Transfer with Serverless AirPods Pro Integration through SFTP, Amazon AWS</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-data-transfer-with-serverless-airpods-pro-integration-through-sftp-amazon-aws/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 17:51:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-data-transfer-with-serverless-airpods-pro-integration-through-sftp-amazon-aws/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Data transfer has always been an issue for most companies as it is difficult to securely send data from one location to the other. The use of Secure File Transfer Protocol (SFTP) and cloud services like Amazon Web Services (AWS) has made the transfer possible but still with some limitations. Our company, ShitOps, faced a similar challenge when we had to transfer large amounts of data daily between two important locations. We tried using available services but found them inefficient, so we started our own research to come up with an outstanding solution. After months of brainstorming and testing, we developed a revolutionary solution that integrated serverless AirPods Pro technology into the existing system to not only ensure secure data transfer but also make the process simpler, faster, and more cost-effective.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>