<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Smart Grids on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/smart-grids/</link><description>Recent content in Smart Grids on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 00:12:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/smart-grids/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Optimizing Multi-Tenant Smart Grids with Dockerized Site-2-Site CCNA Connectivity</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-multi-tenant-smart-grids-with-dockerized-site-2-site-ccna-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 00:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-multi-tenant-smart-grids-with-dockerized-site-2-site-ccna-connectivity/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog, where we explore cutting-edge solutions for complex technical challenges. In this post, we will delve into the optimization of multi-tenant smart grids using a Dockerized approach with Site-2-Site CCNA connectivity. By leveraging the power of VMware NSX-T, Icinga2 monitoring, and Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt for secure certificate management, we can revolutionize the way smart grids are managed in a multi-tenant environment.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-problem-statement">The Problem Statement&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In traditional smart grid deployments, managing multiple tenants within a single infrastructure poses significant challenges. Each tenant requires dedicated resources, isolated networks, and secure connectivity, leading to operational complexity and increased maintenance overhead. Additionally, ensuring real-time monitoring and secure communication between different components of the smart grid is crucial for efficient operations.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Optimizing Telemetry Data Processing in Smart Grids using Elliptic Curve Cryptography</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-telemetry-data-processing-in-smart-grids-using-elliptic-curve-cryptography/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-telemetry-data-processing-in-smart-grids-using-elliptic-curve-cryptography/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/optimizing-telemetry-data-processing-in-smart-grids-using-elliptic-curve-cryptography.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to another exciting blog post from the engineering team at ShitOps! Today, we are going to dive deep into the world of smart grids and explore how we can optimize the telemetry data processing using the power of elliptic curve cryptography (ECC). But first, let&amp;rsquo;s take a moment to understand the problem we are trying to solve.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-problem">The Problem&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As the demand for renewable energy increases, more and more smart grids are being deployed to efficiently manage and distribute power. These smart grids heavily rely on telemetry data gathered from various devices such as sensors, meters, and actuators. However, processing this vast amount of telemetry data in real-time poses a significant challenge.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How Hyperautomation and Django Saved Our Mobile App from Business Intelligence Dilemmas in Smart Grids</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/how-hyperautomation-and-django-saved-our-mobile-app-from-business-intelligence-dilemmas-in-smart-grids/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/how-hyperautomation-and-django-saved-our-mobile-app-from-business-intelligence-dilemmas-in-smart-grids/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/how-hyperautomation-and-django-saved-our-mobile-app-from-business-intelligence-dilemmas-in-smart-grids.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog! Today, we are thrilled to share our groundbreaking solution that revolutionizes mobile app development in the context of business intelligence and smart grids. In this post, we will delve into the intricate details of our highly innovative approach and unveil how hyperautomation and Django came to the rescue to overcome the most challenging dilemmas faced by our mobile app.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Optimizing Edge Computing in Smart Grids Using GRPC and OSPF</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-edge-computing-in-smart-grids-using-grpc-and-ospf/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 13:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-edge-computing-in-smart-grids-using-grpc-and-ospf/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/optimizing-edge-computing-in-smart-grids-using-grpc-and-ospf.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog! In this post, we are going to explore a groundbreaking solution to optimize edge computing in smart grids using GRPC and OSPF.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Over the past decade, the energy industry has witnessed significant advancements in the field of smart grids. These intelligent power systems leverage advanced communication and control technologies to transform the way electricity is generated, distributed, and consumed. However, one of the key challenges faced by smart grid operators is the efficient utilization of edge computing resources for real-time monitoring, analysis, and decision-making.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>