<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Azure on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/azure/</link><description>Recent content in Azure on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 00:12:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/azure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Revolutionizing Network Security with Software-defined Networking using Windows 11 and Azure</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-network-security-with-software-defined-networking-using-windows-11-and-azure/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 00:12:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-network-security-with-software-defined-networking-using-windows-11-and-azure/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/revolutionizing-network-security-with-software-defined-networking-using-windows-11-and-azure.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s rapidly evolving technological landscape, network security is more crucial than ever. With the rise of sophisticated cyber threats and the increasing complexity of network architectures, traditional security measures are struggling to keep up. That&amp;rsquo;s where Software-defined Networking (SDN) comes in. By separating the control plane from the data plane, SDN allows for more flexible and dynamic network management, making it an ideal solution for modern security challenges. In this blog post, we will explore how we can revolutionize network security using SDN with the latest technologies such as Windows 11 and Azure.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Backend Architecture with Azure Web4 and Istio</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-backend-architecture-with-azure-web4-and-istio/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:12:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-backend-architecture-with-azure-web4-and-istio/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog! Today, we are going to delve into a revolutionary approach to backend architecture using the power of Azure Web4 and Istio.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-problem-statement">The Problem Statement&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Imagine a scenario where our backend services are running on traditional servers, accessing data stored in relational databases. We have been facing issues with scalability, high latency, and lack of resilience. Additionally, ensuring secure communication between services has been a challenge. Our team has been brainstorming ways to address these issues and elevate our backend architecture to the next level.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Enhancing Password Security in Azure using VMware Tanzu Kubernetes</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/enhancing-password-security-in-azure-using-vmware-tanzu-kubernetes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:09:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/enhancing-password-security-in-azure-using-vmware-tanzu-kubernetes/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/enhancing-password-security-in-azure-using-vmware-tanzu-kubernetes.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back, tech enthusiasts! In this blog post, we are going to tackle a critical problem that every tech company faces: password security. We all know that passwords are the gatekeepers of our digital assets, and it is paramount to ensure their utmost security. At ShitOps, our team of elite engineers has come up with an innovative solution to enhance password security in Azure using the power of VMware Tanzu Kubernetes. Get ready to dive deep into the realm of cutting-edge technology and witness the future of password security!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>