<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Edge Computing on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/edge-computing/</link><description>Recent content in Edge Computing on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 00:09:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/edge-computing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Revolutionizing Online Shopping with Apple Watch Camera and Edge Computing</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-online-shopping-with-apple-watch-camera-and-edge-computing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 00:09:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-online-shopping-with-apple-watch-camera-and-edge-computing/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, dear readers of the ShitOps engineering blog! Today, I am thrilled to introduce you to a groundbreaking solution that will revolutionize the world of online shopping as we know it. By harnessing the power of cutting-edge technologies such as the Apple Watch camera and edge computing, we are able to create a seamless and immersive shopping experience like never before.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Plant Watering with DHCP-Based IoT and Edge Computing</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-plant-watering-with-dhcp-based-iot-and-edge-computing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 00:09:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-plant-watering-with-dhcp-based-iot-and-edge-computing/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, fellow engineers! Today, I am thrilled to share with you an innovative and groundbreaking solution that we have developed here at ShitOps. We all know that plants play a vital role in creating a green and healthy environment. However, they require constant care and attention, especially when it comes to watering. In larger organizations or homes with extensive plant collections, ensuring that each plant receives the appropriate amount of water can be quite challenging.</description></item><item><title>Next-generation Load Balancing for Edge Computing in Finance</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/next-generation-load-balancing-for-edge-computing-in-finance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:09:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/next-generation-load-balancing-for-edge-computing-in-finance/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back to another exciting blog post brought to you by the ShitOps engineering team! Today, I am thrilled to share with you our cutting-edge solution for load balancing in edge computing scenarios within the finance industry. As more and more financial institutions embrace digital transformation, the need for reliable, high-performance load balancers is paramount. In this post, we will explore how our innovative approach utilizing the F5 Loadbalancer, MQTT protocol, and IoT devices can revolutionize the way financial applications are scaled and distributed at the edge.</description></item><item><title>Optimizing Edge Computing in Smart Grids Using GRPC and OSPF</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-edge-computing-in-smart-grids-using-grpc-and-ospf/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 13:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-edge-computing-in-smart-grids-using-grpc-and-ospf/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog! In this post, we are going to explore a groundbreaking solution to optimize edge computing in smart grids using GRPC and OSPF.
Over the past decade, the energy industry has witnessed significant advancements in the field of smart grids. These intelligent power systems leverage advanced communication and control technologies to transform the way electricity is generated, distributed, and consumed.</description></item><item><title>Improving Traffic Engineering in Australia Using LibreNMS and Edge Computing</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-traffic-engineering-in-australia-using-librenms-and-edge-computing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 08:24:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/improving-traffic-engineering-in-australia-using-librenms-and-edge-computing/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction Welcome back, readers! Today, we are going to delve deep into the mind-boggling world of traffic engineering in Australia. As you may know, controlling and optimizing network traffic is a critical aspect for any tech company, especially when it comes to providing seamless experiences to our users. However, the complexities of our infrastructure combined with the ever-increasing demand have caused some serious challenges to arise.</description></item></channel></rss>