<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lambda Functions on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/lambda-functions/</link><description>Recent content in Lambda Functions on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 11:35:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/lambda-functions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Solving DNS Resolution Issues at Scale with Microsoft, GNMI, Juniper, Mainframe, Mesh, Self Hosting, Lambda Functions and Open Source</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/solving-dns-resolution-issues-at-scale-with-microsoft-gnmi-juniper-mainframe-mesh-self-hosting-lambda-functions-and-open-source/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 11:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/solving-dns-resolution-issues-at-scale-with-microsoft-gnmi-juniper-mainframe-mesh-self-hosting-lambda-functions-and-open-source/</guid><description>Listen to the interview with our engineer: Introduction DNS resolution is a critical part of the network infrastructure for any tech company. It helps in resolving human-readable domain names into IP addresses and vice versa, but at the cost of adding latency to network requests, which can further impact the performance of applications that depend on them.
Recently, our tech company ShitOps faced a DNS resolution issue at scale, due to the increasing number of services added on the network infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Loadbalancing with Nintendo DS and Headphones</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-loadbalancing-with-nintendo-ds-and-headphones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:07:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-loadbalancing-with-nintendo-ds-and-headphones/</guid><description>Introduction As our company grew in size, we found that our Windows Server-based loadbalancing solution was no longer efficient enough to serve our customer&amp;rsquo;s requests. We needed to find a new solution, but with so many options available, it was difficult to make the right choice.
After spending countless hours brainstorming and experimenting with different ideas, we finally struck upon a unique solution; what if we could employ Nintendo DS consoles, coupled with headphones, for a state of the art load balancing solution?</description></item></channel></rss>