<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lambda Functions on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</title><link>https://shitops.de/tags/lambda-functions/</link><description>Recent content in Lambda Functions on Technical Solutions for the 10X Engineers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 00:12:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shitops.de/tags/lambda-functions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Optimizing Data Transfer Speed with Dockerized Rsync and Lambda Functions</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-data-transfer-speed-with-dockerized-rsync-and-lambda-functions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 00:12:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/optimizing-data-transfer-speed-with-dockerized-rsync-and-lambda-functions/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/optimizing-data-transfer-speed-with-dockerized-rsync-and-lambda-functions.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Welcome back to the ShitOps engineering blog, where we dive deep into solving complex technical challenges with cutting-edge solutions. In today&amp;rsquo;s post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how we can optimize data transfer speed using a combination of Dockerized Rsync and serverless Lambda functions.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-problem">The Problem&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>At ShitOps, we often encounter the need to transfer large amounts of data between servers in different regions. Traditional methods of transferring data, such as SCP or FTP, are not efficient enough for our needs. We require a solution that can handle concurrent transfers, ensure data integrity, and scale seamlessly with our growing infrastructure.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Deployment with Golang and Ethereum Smart Contracts</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-deployment-with-golang-and-ethereum-smart-contracts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:10:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-deployment-with-golang-and-ethereum-smart-contracts/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/revolutionizing-deployment-with-golang-and-ethereum-smart-contracts.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>At ShitOps, we constantly strive to push the boundaries of technology and revolutionize the way we approach deployment processes. In this blog post, we will delve into a groundbreaking solution that leverages the power of Golang and Ethereum smart contracts to streamline our deployment pipelines.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-problem">The Problem&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>One of the key challenges we have faced at ShitOps is the lack of transparency and security in our deployment process. Our existing methods rely on traditional CI/CD tools like GitLab, which can be vulnerable to unauthorized access and malicious attacks. Additionally, the manual intervention required for deploying updates has led to inefficiencies and delays in our release cycles.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Solving DNS Resolution Issues at Scale with Microsoft, GNMI, Juniper, Mainframe, Mesh, Self Hosting, Lambda Functions and Open Source</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/solving-dns-resolution-issues-at-scale-with-microsoft-gnmi-juniper-mainframe-mesh-self-hosting-lambda-functions-and-open-source/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 11:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/solving-dns-resolution-issues-at-scale-with-microsoft-gnmi-juniper-mainframe-mesh-self-hosting-lambda-functions-and-open-source/</guid><description>&lt;p>Listen to the interview with our engineer: &lt;figure class="audio">
&lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
&lt;source src="https://s3.chaops.de/shitops/podcasts/solving-dns-resolution-issues-at-scale-with-microsoft-gnmi-juniper-mainframe-mesh-self-hosting-lambda-functions-and-open-source.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">

&lt;/audio>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>DNS resolution is a critical part of the network infrastructure for any tech company. It helps in resolving human-readable domain names into IP addresses and vice versa, but at the cost of adding latency to network requests, which can further impact the performance of applications that depend on them.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Recently, our tech company ShitOps faced a DNS resolution issue at scale, due to the increasing number of services added on the network infrastructure. We realized that the traditional approach of using a central DNS server was no longer sufficient to handle this scale.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Revolutionizing Loadbalancing with Nintendo DS and Headphones</title><link>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-loadbalancing-with-nintendo-ds-and-headphones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:07:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shitops.de/posts/revolutionizing-loadbalancing-with-nintendo-ds-and-headphones/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As our company grew in size, we found that our Windows Server-based loadbalancing solution was no longer efficient enough to serve our customer&amp;rsquo;s requests. We needed to find a new solution, but with so many options available, it was difficult to make the right choice.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After spending countless hours brainstorming and experimenting with different ideas, we finally struck upon a unique solution; what if we could employ Nintendo DS consoles, coupled with headphones, for a state of the art load balancing solution? And what if we told you that we&amp;rsquo;ve managed to incorporate lambda functions and embedded these Nintendo DS consoles into our server network?&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>